<de-DE>
12.9:
* Customers with unclaimed domain credits can register domains in the app.
* You can expand the Comment Editor to Full Screen for more space while editing.
* The Block editor has a few improvements: Video blocks are available, and a some issues that led to content loss when using unsupported blocks have been resolved.
</de-DE>
<en-US>
12.9:
* Customers with unclaimed domain credits can register domains in the app.
* You can expand the Comment Editor to Full Screen for more space while editing.
* The Block editor has a few improvements: Video blocks are available, and a some issues that led to content loss when using unsupported blocks have been resolved.
</en-US>
<es-ES>
12.9:
* Los clientes con créditos de dominio no reclamados pueden registrar dominios en la aplicación.
* Puedes expandir el editor de comentarios a pantalla completa para tener más espacio durante la edición.
* El editor de bloques tiene algunas mejoras: Los bloques de vídeo ya están disponibles, y se han resuelto algunos problemas que llevaron a la pérdida de contenido cuando se utilizaban bloques no compatibles.
</es-ES>
<fr-CA>
12.9:
* Customers with unclaimed domain credits can register domains in the app.
* You can expand the Comment Editor to Full Screen for more space while editing.
* The Block editor has a few improvements: Video blocks are available, and a some issues that led to content loss when using unsupported blocks have been resolved.
</fr-CA>
<fr-FR>
12.9:
* Customers with unclaimed domain credits can register domains in the app.
* You can expand the Comment Editor to Full Screen for more space while editing.
* The Block editor has a few improvements: Video blocks are available, and a some issues that led to content loss when using unsupported blocks have been resolved.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
12.9:
* Customers with unclaimed domain credits can register domains in the app.
* You can expand the Comment Editor to Full Screen for more space while editing.
* The Block editor has a few improvements: Video blocks are available, and a some issues that led to content loss when using unsupported blocks have been resolved.
</iw-IL>
<it-IT>
12.9:
* Customers with unclaimed domain credits can register domains in the app.
* You can expand the Comment Editor to Full Screen for more space while editing.
* The Block editor has a few improvements: Video blocks are available, and a some issues that led to content loss when using unsupported blocks have been resolved.
</it-IT>
<nl-NL>
12.9:
* Customers with unclaimed domain credits can register domains in the app.
* You can expand the Comment Editor to Full Screen for more space while editing.
* The Block editor has a few improvements: Video blocks are available, and a some issues that led to content loss when using unsupported blocks have been resolved.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
12.9:
* Usuários com crédito de domínios disponíveis podem registrar domínios no aplicativo.
* Você pode expandir o editor de comentários para tela cheia para ter mais espaço ao editar.
* Algumas melhorias no editor de blocos: blocos de vídeo estão disponíveis e corrigimos alguns erros com perda de conteúdo ao usar blocos não suportados.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
12.9:
* Пользователи с неиспользованной ещё возможностью зарегистрировать домен теперь могут сделать это прямо из приложения.
* Редактор комментариев при редактировании можно развернуть на весь экран.
* Улучшения в редакторе блоков: доступны блоки видео, исправлена проблема с возможной потерей данных при использовании неподдерживаемых блоков.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
12.9:
* Kunder som inte utnyttjat sin fulla domänkredit kan registrera domäner i appen.
* Du kan expandera kommentarsredigeraren så att den upptar hela skärmen, för mer utrymmen när du redigerar.
* Några förbättringar i blockredigeraren: Nu finns videoblock, och några problem som kunde leda till förlorat innehåll vid användning av block utan stöd har nu lösts.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
12.9:
* Sahipsiz alan adı kredisi olan müşteriler, alan adlarını uygulamaya kaydedebilir.
* Düzenleme sırasında daha fazla yer açmak için yorum düzenleyiciyi tam ekrana genişletebilirsiniz.
* Blok düzenleyicinin birkaç geliştirmesi var: Video blokları var ve desteklenmeyen blokları kullanırken içerik kaybına neden olan bazı sorunlar çözüldü.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
12.9:
* Customers with unclaimed domain credits can register domains in the app.
* You can expand the Comment Editor to Full Screen for more space while editing.
* The Block editor has a few improvements:Video blocks are available, and a some issues that led to content loss when using unsupported blocks have been resolved.
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
12.9:
* Customers with unclaimed domain credits can register domains in the app.
* You can expand the Comment Editor to Full Screen for more space while editing.
* The Block editor has a few improvements:Video blocks are available, and a some issues that led to content loss when using unsupported blocks have been resolved.
</zh-TW>
