<ar>
15.1:
تحسينات: تنبثق لوحة الجدولة والوسم والرؤية في المحرِّر والنشر السابق لقائمة المقالات. يؤدي الضغط على مفتاح "enter"، بعد إضافة التسميات التوضيحية في مكوِّنات الصورة والفيديو والمعرض والاقتباس والمكوِّن المهيأ مسبقًا، إلى إضافة مكوِّن جديد.

الإصلاحات: تظهر الصور المصغَّرة للفيديوهات والإعدادات والمعاينة بشكل صحيح على المواقع الخاصة. لا تتراكب التنبيهات وعلامات تبويب "تثبيت Jetpack" بعد الآن.
</ar>
<de-DE>
15.1:
 Verbesserungen: Bereich für Planen, Schlagwörter und Sichtbarkeit wird im Editor und der Vorab-Veröffentlichung der Beitragsliste angezeigt. Wenn du nach dem Hinzufügen von Beschriftungen in Bild-, Video-, Galerie-, Zitat- und Pullquote-Blöcken die Eingabetaste drückst, wird ein neuer Block hinzugefügt.

Korrekturen: Vorschaubilder, Einstellungen und die Vorschau für Videos werden auf privaten Websites richtig angezeigt. Die Tabs für Benachrichtigungen und "Jetpack installieren" überschneiden sich nicht mehr.
</de-DE>
<en-US>
15.1:
Block editor improvements: Scheduling, tag, and visibility settings pop up in the post editor and post list when you tap Publish — tweak them and tap “Publish Now” to complete publication. Pressing enter after adding a caption in Image, Video, Gallery, Quote, and Pullquote blocks automatically adds a new block.

Fixes: Video thumbnails, settings, and preview display properly in the Media section on private sites. Notifications and Install Jetpack tabs no longer display on top of one another.
</en-US>
<es-ES>
15.1:
Mejoras: Mensajes emergentes de programación, etiquetas y visibilidad en el panel de lista previa a la publicación del editor. Pulsando intro tras añadir leyendas en bloques de imagen, vídeo, galería, cita y bloque de cita añade un nuevo bloque.

Correcciones: Miniaturas de vídeo, ajustes y visualización de vista previa correctas en los sitios privados. Los avisos y pestañas de instalación de JetPack ya no se superponen.
</es-ES>
<fr-CA>
15.1 :
Améliorations : le volet de planification, étiquette et visibilité s’affiche dans l’éditeur et lors de la pré-publication de la liste d’articles. Appuyer sur Entrée après l’ajout d’une légende dans un bloc Image, Vidéo, Galerie, Citation ou Citation en exergue ajoute un nouveau bloc.

Corrections : les miniatures de vidéo, les paramètres et les aperçus s’affichent correctement sur les sites privés. Les onglets Notifications et Installer Jetpack ne se superposent plus.
</fr-CA>
<fr-FR>
15.1 :
Améliorations : le volet de planification, étiquette et visibilité s’affiche dans l’éditeur et lors de la pré-publication de la liste d’articles. Appuyer sur Entrée après l’ajout d’une légende dans un bloc Image, Vidéo, Galerie, Citation ou Citation en exergue ajoute un nouveau bloc.

Corrections : les miniatures de vidéo, les paramètres et les aperçus s’affichent correctement sur les sites privés. Les onglets Notifications et Installer Jetpack ne se superposent plus.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
15.1:
שיפורים: הודעות לגבי קביעת לוח זמנים, תגיות וחלונית הנראות מופיעות כעת בחלון קופץ בעורך וברשימת הפוסטים לפני הפרסום. לחיצה על Enter אחרי הוספת תיאור לבלוקים של תמונה, וידאו, גלריה וציטוט מוסיפה בלוק חדש. 

תיקונים: תמונות ממוזערות, הגדרות ותצוגות מקדימות של סרטוני וידאו מוצגות כעת בצורה תקינה באתרים פרטיים. הלשוניות 'הודעות' ו-'להתקין את Jetpack' לא מופיעות עוד זו על גבי זו.
</iw-IL>
<id>
15.1:
Peningkatan: Penjadwalan, tag, dan panel visibilitas muncul di penyunting dan daftar pos sebelum publikasi. Menekan tombol enter setelah menambahkan keterangan di blok Gambar, Video, Galeri, Kutipan, Kutipan Besar akan menambahkan blok baru.

Perbaikan: Thumbnail video, pengaturan, dan pratinjau ditampilkan dengan benar di situs pribadi. Tab Pemberiahuan dan Pemasangan Jetpack tidak lagi saling menghalangi.
</id>
<it-IT>
15.1:
Miglioramenti: pianificazione, tag e pop up del pannello della visibilità nell'editor e nella prepubblicazione dell'elenco degli articoli. Premendo il tasto per l'inserimento dopo aver aggiunto didascalie in un blocco Immagine, Video, Galleria, Citazione o Citazione evidenziata si aggiunge un nuovo blocco.

Correzioni: miniature dei video, impostazioni e anteprima visualizzati in modo corretto sui siti privati. Le schede Notifiche e Installazione di Jetpack non sono più sovrapposte
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
15.1: 
ブロックエディターの改善 :「公開」をタップすると投稿エディターと投稿リストにスケジュール設定、タグ設定、公開設定のポップアップが表示されます。これらを編集して「今すぐ公開」をタップすると、公開が完了します。 画像、動画、ギャラリー、引用、プルクオートブロックにキャプションを追加して Enter を押すと、新しいブロックが自動で作成されます。

修正 : 非公開サイトの「メディア」セクションで、動画のサムネイル、設定、プレビューが正しく表示されるようになりました。 「通知」タブと「Jetpack をインストール」タブが重なって表示されなくなりました。
</ja-JP>
<nl-NL>
15.1:
Verbeteringen: het venster voor planning, tags en zichtbaarheid komt tevoorschijn in de editor en in de voorpublicatie van berichtlijsten. Door op enter te drukken na het toevoegen van bijschriften aan een Afbeelding-, Video-, Galerij-, Citaat- en Pullquote-blok wordt een nieuw blok toegevoegd.

Fixes: video-miniatuurweergaven, instellingen en voorbeeldweergaven worden nu op de juiste manier weergegeven op privésites. Geen overlap meer van de tabbladen Meldingen en Installeren van Jetpack.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
15.1:
Melhorias no editor de blocos: Agendamento, tag e configurações de visibilidade são exibidos no editor de post e lista de posts ao tocar em Publicar. Faça os ajustes necessários e toque em "Publicar agora" para concluir a publicação. Pressionar Enter após adicionar uma legenda nos blocos de Imagem, Vídeo ou Citação agora adiciona um novo bloco automaticamente.

Correções: Miniaturas de vídeo, configurações e visualização são exibidos corretamente na seção Mídia em sites privados. As abas Notificações e Instalar Jetpack não são mais exibidas uma sobre a outra.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
15.1:
Улучшения в редакторе блоков: планирование метки и настройки видимости в всплыващей панели. Список записей при нажатии на кнопку публикации, вы можете настроить их и опубликовать. Добавление нового блока автоматически после ввода подписи для изображений, галерей, видео и цитат.

Исправления: миниатюры видео, настройки и предпросмотр в мультимедиа разделе личных сайтов будут корректными. Уведомления и вкладки установки Jetpack более не перекрывают друг друга.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
15.1:
Förbättringar: schemaläggning, tagg och synlighetspanelen poppar upp i redigeringsprogrammet och inläggslistan innan publicering. Tryck Retur efter att du lagt till bildtexter i Bild-, Video-, Galleri- eller Citat-block så läggs ett nytt block till automatiskt.

Korrigeringar: videominiatyrer, inställningar och förhandsvisning visas korrekt på privata webbplatser. Flikarna Meddelanden och Installera Jetpack visas inte längre ovanpå varandra.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
15.1:
İyileştirmeler: Zamanlama, etiket ve görünürlük paneli, editör ve yazı listesi ön yayınında açılır. Görsel, video, galeri, alıntı ve tanıtım bloklarına başlıkı ekledikten sonra enter tuşuna basıldığında yeni bir blok eklenir.

Düzeltmeler: Video küçük resimleri, ayarları ve önizlemesi özel sitelerde düzgün bir şekilde görüntülenir. Bildirimler ve Jetpack yükle sekmeleri artık üst üste binmiyor.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
15.1：
区块编辑器改进：当您点按“发布”时，文章编辑器和文章列表中会弹出预发布、标签和可见性设置 - 调整设置并点按“立即发布”即可完成发布。 在图片、视频、图库、引用或醒目引文区块中添加说明之后按 Enter 键，即可自动添加新区块。

修复：视频缩略图、设置和预览在私人站点上的“媒体”部分正确显示。 “通知”和“安装 Jetpack”选项卡不再叠加显示。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
15.1：
區塊編輯器改善功能：點選「發表」後，文章編輯器和文章清單會彈出排程、標籤和能見度設定。調整這些設定後點選「立即發表」，即可完成文章發表。 在圖片、影片、圖庫、引文和重要引述區塊新增說明後按下 Enter 鍵，系統會自動新增一個區塊。

修正項目：影片縮圖、設定和預覽會在私人網站的「媒體」區段正確顯示。 「通知」和「安裝 Jetpack」分頁不再重疊顯示。
</zh-TW>
