<ar>
13.6:
- قمنا بتحديث لون شريط التنقل إلى اللون الأبيض على نظام التشغيل Android 8.1 والإصدارات الأحدث منه.
- تم إصلاح الأخطاء الواردة في ترتيب قائمة الصفحات، لذا ستظهر الصفحات دائمًا بترتيب أبجدي.
- تحديثات محرِّر المكوّنات: تمت إضافة دعم للصور وخيارات محاذاة الصورة في Pexels.

</ar>
<de-DE>
13.6:
- Wir haben die Farbe der Navigationsleiste in Android 8.1 oder höher auf Weiß aktualisiert.
- Ein Fehler beim Sortieren von Seiten wurden behoben, sodass Seiten stets in alphabetischer Reihenfolge angezeigt werden.
- Updates im Block-Editor: Support für Pexels-Bilder und Optionen zum Ausrichten von Bildern hinzugefügt.

</de-DE>
<en-US>
13.6:
- We updated the navigation bar color to white on Android 8.1 and higher.
- Bugs in page list ordering are fixed, so pages always appear in alphabetical order.
- Block editor updates: Added support for Pexels images and image alignment options.

</en-US>
<es-ES>
13.6:
- Hemos actualizado el color de la barra de navegación a blanco en Android 8.1 y superior.
- Los fallos en el orden de la lista de páginas han sido corregidos, por lo que las páginas siempre aparecen en orden alfabético.
- Actualizaciones del editor de bloques: Añadida compatibilidad para imágenes de Pexels y opciones de alineación de imágenes.
</es-ES>
<fr-CA>
13.6:
- We updated the navigation bar color to white on Android 8.1 and higher.
- Bugs in page list ordering are fixed, so pages always appear in alphabetical order.
- Block editor updates: Added support for Pexels images and image alignment options.

</fr-CA>
<fr-FR>
13.6:
- We updated the navigation bar color to white on Android 8.1 and higher.
- Bugs in page list ordering are fixed, so pages always appear in alphabetical order.
- Block editor updates: Added support for Pexels images and image alignment options.

</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
13.6:
- שינינו את הצבע של סרגל הניווט ללבן ב-Android 8.1 ומעלה.
- תוקנו הבאגים בסידור רשימת העמודים כך שהעמודים תמיד יופיעו בסדר אלפביתי.
- עדכונים בעורך הבלוקים: הוספנו תמיכה בתמונות Pexels ובאפשרויות יישור תמונה.

</iw-IL>
<id>
13.6:
- Kami memperbarui warna bilah navigasi menjadi putih di Android 8.1 dan yang lebih tinggi.
- Bug di pengurutan daftar halaman telah diperbaiki, sehingga halaman selalu ditampilkan dalam urutan alfabet.
* Pembaruan penyunting blok: Dukungan yang ditambahkan untuk gambar Pexels dan pilihan penyelarasan gambar.

</id>
<it-IT>
13.6:
- Abbiamo aggiornato il colore della barra di navigazione al bianco su Android 8.1 e versioni successione.
- I bug nell'ordinamento dell'elenco di pagine sono stati risolti, quindi le pagine saranno sempre visualizzate in ordine alfabetico.
* Aggiornamenti all'editor dei blocchi: aggiunto supporto per immagini Pexels e opzioni per l'allineamento delle immagini.

</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
13.6:
- Android 8.1以降で、ナビゲーションバーの色が白に変更されました。
- ページリストの順序についてのバグが修正され、ページが常にアルファベット順に表示されるようになりました。
- ブロックエディターの更新 :Pexels 画像対応となり、画像の配置オプションが追加されました。

</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
13.6:
- Android 8.1 이상에서 탐색 표시줄 색을 흰색으로 업데이트했습니다.
- 페이지 목록 순서의 버그가 수정되어 페이지가 항상 알파벳순으로 표시됩니다.
- 블록 편집기 업데이트: Pexels 이미지 및 이미지 정렬 옵션에 대한 지원이 추가되었습니다.

</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
13.6:
- We hebben de kleur van de navigatiebalk op Android 8.1 en hoger bijgewerkt naar wit.
- Bugs die voor problemen zorgden met de sortering van de paginalijst zijn verwijderd, zodat pagina's altijd in alfabetische volgorde worden weergegeven.
* Updates van de blokeditor: Ondersteuning voor Pexels-afbeeldingen en opties voor uitlijning van afbeeldingen toegevoegd.

</nl-NL>
<ru-RU>
13.6:
- Цвет панели навигации изменен на белый для Android 8.1 и выше
- Исправлена ошибка отображения списка страниц, теперь они всегда будут упорядочены по алфавиту.
- Обновление редактора блоков: Поддержка изображений с Pexels и возможности выравнивания изображений.

</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
13.6:
- Vi har uppdaterat navigationslisten färg till vitt i Android 8.1 och senare.
- Fel i sorteringen av listan med sidor har rättats så att sidorna alltid ska visas i bokstavsordning.
- Uppdateringar av blockredigeraren: Stöd för Pexels-bilder och justering av bilder i sidled.

</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
13.6:
- Gezinti çubuğunun rengini Android 8.1 ve üzeri sürümlerde beyaza dönüştürdük.
- Sayfa listesindeki hatalar düzeltildi, bu yüzden sayfalar her zaman alfabetik sırada görünüyor.
- Block düzenleyici güncellemeleri: Pexels görselleri ve görüntü hizalama seçenekleri için destek eklendi.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
13.6：
- 在 Android 8.1 及更高版本中，我们已将导航栏颜色更新为白色。
- 修复了页面列表排序中的错误，因此页面始终按字母顺序显示。
- 更新了区块编辑器：增加了对 Pexels 图片和图片对齐选项的支持。

</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
13.6：
- 我們已將 Android 8.1 與更新版本的導覽列顏色改成白色。
- 頁面清單排序的錯誤已經修正，現在頁面將一律依字母順序顯示。
* 區塊編輯器更新：新增對 Pexels 圖片和圖片對齊選項的支援。

</zh-TW>
