<ar>
18.9:
- قم بتمييز النص باستخدام أي لون في مكوِّنات الفقرة.
- اطلع على التعليقات ورد عليها بعد محتوى مقالتك في القارئ.
- قم بإنشاء مكوِّنات معرض جديدة باستخدام التصميم الجديد وقم بتحويل المعارض القديمة تلقائيًا للمطابقة.
- تراجع عن التغييرات وقم بإعادتها عند تنسيق نص الرابط في المكوِّنات.
- قم بالتحميل بشكل أسرع عند إعادة تدوين المقالات ومشاركة نص من تطبيقات أخرى.
</ar>
<de-DE>
18.9:
- Markiere Text im Absatzblöcken mit einer beliebigen Farbe.
- Schau dir unter dem Inhalt deines Beitrags im Reader Kommentare an und beantworte sie.
- Erstelle neue Galerieblöcke mit neuem Design und konvertiere alte Galerien automatisch, damit sie dazu passen.
- Mache Änderungen beim Formatieren von Linktext in Blöcken rückgängig oder stelle sie wieder her.
- Lade Inhalte schneller, wenn du Beiträge rebloggst oder Text aus anderen Apps teilst.
</de-DE>
<en-US>
18.9:
- Highlight text with any color in Paragraph blocks.
- See and respond to comments after your post content in the Reader.
- Create new Gallery blocks with the new design and auto-convert old galleries to match.
- Undo and redo changes when formatting link text in blocks.
- Load faster when reblogging posts and sharing text from other apps.
</en-US>
<es-ES>
18.9:
- Resaltar el texto con cualquier color en los bloques de párrafo.
- Ver y responder a los comentarios en el lector después de tu contenido.
- Crear nuevos bloques de Galería con el nuevo diseño y convertir automáticamente las galerías antiguas para que coincidan.
- Deshacer y rehacer los cambios al formar el texto de los enlaces en los bloques.
- Carga más rápida al volver a bloguear entradas y compartir texto desde otras aplicaciones.
</es-ES>
<fr-CA>
18.9 :
- Surlignez du texte dans n’importe quelle couleur dans les blocs Paragraphe.
- Affichez et répondez aux commentaires après le contenu de votre article dans le Lecteur.
- Créez de blocs Galerie avec le nouveau design et convertissez automatiquement vos anciennes galeries.
- Annulez et rétablissez des modifications lors du formatage de liens dans les blocs.
- Chargement plus rapide lors du reblogging d’articles et du partage de texte depuis d’autres applications.
</fr-CA>
<fr-FR>
18.9 :
- Surlignez du texte dans n’importe quelle couleur dans les blocs Paragraphe.
- Affichez et répondez aux commentaires après le contenu de votre article dans le Lecteur.
- Créez de blocs Galerie avec le nouveau design et convertissez automatiquement vos anciennes galeries.
- Annulez et rétablissez des modifications lors du formatage de liens dans les blocs.
- Chargement plus rapide lors du reblogging d’articles et du partage de texte depuis d’autres applications.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
18.9:
- אפשר להגדיש טקסט בכל צבע שרוצים בבלוקים של פסקה רגילה.
- אפשר לראות תגובות ולהגיב עליהן לאחר פרסום התוכן של הפוסט ב-Reader.
- אפשר ליצור בלוקים חדשים של גלריה עם העיצוב החדש ולהמיר באופן אוטומטי גלריות ישנות כדי להתאים אותן.
- אפשר לבטל שינויים או לבצע אותם שוב כאשר מעצבים טקסט של קישור בבלוקים.
- טעינה מהירה יותר בפרסום מחדש של פוסטים בבלוג ובשיתוף של טקסט מאפליקציות אחרות.
</iw-IL>
<id>
18.9:
- Sorot teks dengan warna apa pun di blok Paragraf.
- Lihat dan berikan respons ke komentar setelah Anda memposkan konten di Pembaca.
- Buat blok Galeri baru dengan desain baru untuk mengonversikan galeri lama secara otomatis agar sesuai.
- Urungkan dan ulangi perubahan saat memformat teks tautan di blok.
- Muat lebih cepat saat melakukan reblog pos dan membagikan teks dari aplikasi lain.
</id>
<it-IT>
18.9:
- Evidenzia il testo con qualsiasi colore nei blocchi Paragrafo.
- Visualizza i commenti e rispondi dopo il contenuto del tuo articolo nel Reader.
- Crea nuovi blocchi Galleria con il nuovo design e converti automaticamente le vecchie gallerie affinché corrispondano.
- Annulla e ripeti le modifiche quando formatti il testo dei link nei blocchi.
- Carica più rapidamente quando ripubblichi articoli e condividi testo da altre app.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
18.9:
- 段落ブロックで任意の色を使ってテキストを強調表示できます。
- Reader でコンテンツを投稿した後で、コメントを見たり、返信したりできます。
- 新しいデザインのギャラリーブロックを作成したり、それに合わせて古いギャラリーを自動変換したりできます。
- ブロック内のリンクテキストの書式を設定する際に、変更を元に戻したり、やり直したりできます。
- 投稿をリブログしたり、他のアプリからテキストを共有したりする際の読み込みが速くなりました。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
18.9:
- 원하는 색상으로 문단 블록의 텍스트를 강조합니다.
- 뉴스피드에서 글 콘텐츠 뒤의 댓글을 보고 답합니다.
- 새 디자인으로 새 갤러리 블록을 생성하고 기존 갤러리가 일치하도록 자동 변환합니다.
- 블록의 링크 텍스트 형식 지정 시 변경사항 실행 취소/재실행이 가능합니다.
- 글을 블로그에 다시 올리고 다른 앱의 텍스트를 공유할 때 더 빨리 로드합니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
18.9:
- Markeer tekst in iedere kleur in paragraafblokken.
- Zie en beantwoord reacties na je berichtinhoud in de Reader.
- Creëer nieuwe galerijblokken met het nieuwe ontwerp, en pas oude galerijen aan zodat ze matchen.
- Maak veranderingen ongedaan of juist opnieuw tijdens het formatteren van link tekst in blokken.
- Snellere laadtijden tijdens het rebloggen van berichten en het delen van tekst uit andere apps.
</nl-NL>
<ru-RU>
18.9:
- Выделяйте текст любым цветом в блоках абзаца.
- Смотрите и отвечайте на комментарии из Чтива, после содержимого записи.
- Создавайте новые блоки галереи с новым дизайном и автоматически конвертируйте старые галереи.
- Отмена и повтор изменений при форматировании текста ссылки в блоках.
- Быстрая загрузка при перепубликации записец и обмене текстом из других приложений.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
18.9:
– Framhäv text med valfri färg i styckblock.
– Läs och besvara kommentarer i Läsaren under inläggets innehåll.
– Skapa nya gallierblock i det nya utförandet och konvertera automatiskt äldre gallerier så att de blir likadana.
– Ångra och gör om ändringar i formateringen av länkad text i block.
– Snabbare sidladdning när du rebloggar inlägg eller delar text från andra appar.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
18.9:
- Paragraf bloklarında metni herhangi bir renkle vurgulayın.
- Okuyucudaki içeriğinizden sonra yorumları görün ve yanıtlayın.
- Yeni tasarımla yeni Galeri blokları oluşturun ve eski galerileri eşleşecek şekilde otomatik olarak dönüştürün.
- Bloklar halinde bağlantı metnini biçimlendirirken değişiklikleri geri alın ve yineleyin.
- Gönderileri yeniden bloga eklerken ve diğer uygulamalardan metin paylaşırken daha hızlı yükleyin.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
18.9：
- 在段落区块中，使用任意颜色突出显示文本。
- 在阅读器中，在文章内容下方查看和回复评论。
- 创建采用最新设计的画廊区块，自动转换旧画廊区块，保持风格一致。
- 在区块中设置链接文本的格式时，撤消和重新更改。
- 重新发布博文和分享来自其他应用程序的文本时，更快加载。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
18.9：
- 在段落區塊中以任何顏色醒目標示文字。
- 在閱讀器的文章內容下方查看並回應留言。
- 建立全新設計的圖庫區塊，並自動轉換舊版圖庫以配合新版設計。
- 在區塊中設定連結文字格式時，可復原和取消復原變更。
- 從其他應用程式轉發文章和分享文字時，載入速度更快。
</zh-TW>
