<ar>
13.8:
* تحسينات محرِّر المكوّن: تمت إضافة مكوّن المباعد لإنشاء مسافة بيضاء بين المحتوى.
* تم تعديل البحث عن المقالات لتضمين المقالات أسفل كل التصنيفات.
* الكثير من التحسينات التي أجريت في الخلفية عبر التطبيق بالكامل – 26 من الإصلاحات الفريدة للأخطاء والأعطال إجمالاً.

</ar>
<de-DE>
13.8:
* Verbesserungen am Block-Editor: Der Abstandshalter-Block wurde hinzugefügt, damit du Leerräume zwischen Inhalten erstellen kannst.
* Die Suche nach Blogbeiträgen wurde verändert, um Beiträge unter allen Kategorien einzuschließen.
* Die gesamte App wurde hinter den Kulissen an zahlreichen Stellen verbessert. Insgesamt wurden 26 Fehler, die zu Abstürzen und Problemen führten, behoben.

</de-DE>
<en-US>
13.8:
* Block editor improvements: Added Spacer block for creating white space between content.
* Modified Blog Post Search to include posts under all categories.
* Lots of under-the-hood improvements across the entire app –26 unique crash and bug fixes in all.

</en-US>
<es-ES>
13.8:
* Mejoras en el editor de bloques: Añadido bloque espaciador para crear espacios vacíos entre contenidos.
* Modificada la búsqueda de entradas del blog para incluir entradas en todas las categorías.
* Montones de mejoras bajo el capó en toda la aplicación  26 correcciones de errores y problemas en total.

</es-ES>
<fr-CA>
13.8 :
* Améliorations de l'éditeur de blocs : un bloc d'espacement a été ajouté pour créer un espace blanc entre le contenu.
* Modification de la recherche d'articles de blog pour inclure les articles appartenant à toutes les catégories.
* Nombreuses améliorations en arrière-plan dans toute l'application. Résolution de 26 bugs ou pannes uniques.

</fr-CA>
<fr-FR>
13.8 :
* Améliorations de l'éditeur de blocs : un bloc d'espacement a été ajouté pour créer un espace blanc entre le contenu.
* Modification de la recherche d'articles de blog pour inclure les articles appartenant à toutes les catégories.
* Nombreuses améliorations en arrière-plan dans toute l'application. Résolution de 26 bugs ou pannes uniques.

</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
13.8:
* שיפורים בעורך הבלוקים: הוספנו את בלוק המרווח כדי ליצור רווח ריק בין התכנים.
* שינינו את חיפוש הפוסטים כדי לכלול פוסטים שמשויכים לכל הקטגוריות.
* ביצענו המון שיפורים מתחת למכסה המנוע ברחבי האפליקציה – תיקנו 26 מקרים ייחודיים של קריסות ובאגים סך הכול.

</iw-IL>
<id>
13.8:
* Peningkatan penyunting blok: Menambahkan blok Spacer untuk membuat spasi putih di antara konten.
* Memodifikasi Pencarian Pos Blog untuk menyertakan pos di semua kategori.
* Banyak peningkatan di seluruh aplikasi – Memperbaiki 26 crash dan bug unik.

</id>
<it-IT>
13.8:
*Miglioramenti all'editor dei blocchi: blocco Spazio vuoto aggiunto per la creazione di spazio bianco tra i contenuti.
*Ricerca dell'articolo del blog modificata per includere gli articoli presenti in tutte le categorie.
*Molti miglioramenti sotto controllo nell'intera app, 26 arresti univoci e correzioni di bug in tutti.

</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
13.8 :
* ブロックエディターの改善 :コンテンツ間に空白を作成するためのスペーサーブロックが追加されました。
* すべてのカテゴリーの投稿を含めるようにブログ投稿検索が変更されました。
* アプリ全体でさまざまな改善がなされ、合計26個の固有のクラッシュとバグが修正されました。

</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
13.8:
* 블록 편집기 개선 사항: 콘텐츠 사이에 공백을 만들기 위한 스페이서 블록을 추가했습니다.
* 모든 카테고리에 글을 포함하도록 블로그 글 검색을 수정했습니다.
* 앱 내부 전체에서 많은 부분이 개선되었습니다(고유한 충돌 및 버그 수정 총 26개).

</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
13.8:
* Verbeteringen aan de blok-editor: Vulelementblok toegevoegd voor het creëren van lege ruimte tussen content.
* De zoekfunctie voor blogberichten is aangepast en bevat nu berichten onder alle categorieën.
* Veel onopvallende verbeteringen in de gehele app: in totaal 26 unieke crash-oplossingen en bugverwijderingen.

</nl-NL>
<ru-RU>
13.8:
* Улучшения в редакторе блоков: добавлен блок-заполнитель, для добавления пустого места между содержимым.
* Поиск по записям в блоге будут включать записи во всех рубриках.
* Целая куча исправлений ошибок и падений (26).
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
13.8:
* Förbättringar i blockredigeraren: Nytt distanselement som kan skapa avstånd mellan olika innehållsblock.
* Sökfunktionen för blogginlägg har modifierats så att den söker inom alla kategorier.
* En rad förbättringar ”under motorhuven” i hela appen. Totalt 26 avhjälpta kraschorsaker och andra fel.

</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
13.8:
* Blok düzenleyici iyileştirmeleri: İçerik arasında beyaz boşluk oluşturmak için Spacer bloğu eklendi.
* Blog Gönderi Arama tüm kategorilerin altındaki gönderileri içerecek şekilde değiştirildi.
* Tüm uygulama içinde görünmeyen bir çok iyileştirme yapıldı -26 benzersiz kapanma ve hata düzeltmeleri.

</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
13.8：
* 区块编辑器改进：添加了用于在内容之间创建空白的空白区块。
* 修改了博文搜索，将文章包含在所有类别下。
* 在整个应用程序中进行了许多改进，包括全部 26 个独特的崩溃和错误修复。

</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
13.8：
* 改善區塊編輯器：新增空白間隔區塊，你現可在內容之間建立空白字元。
* 修改網誌文章搜尋功能，納入所有類別底下的文章。
* 應用程式整體內部改善，一共修正 26 個不同的當機問題和錯誤。

</zh-TW>
