<ar>
14.1:
- محرر المكون: يتيح لك مكون الكود القصير الجديد إنشاء أكواد قصيرة وتعديلها، وقد قمنا بتقليل الحشو حول المكونات النصية، وأصبح تحرير المقالات الطويلة جدًا الآن بمنزلة تجربة أكثر استقرارًا.
- التحديثات: تم تعطيل خيار إزالة موقع Jetpack من منتقي المواقع.
- إصلاحات الأخطاء: حذفت عمليات البحث عن المقالات بعض النتائج. يجري الآن البحث بالشكل المطلوب!



</ar>
<de-DE>
14.1:
- Block-Editor: Mit dem neuen Shortcode-Block kannst du Shortcodes erstellen und bearbeiten, wir haben die Abstände um textbasierte Blöcke verringert und sehr lange Beiträge lassen sich nun stabiler bearbeiten.
- Updates: Die Option zum Entfernen einer Jetpack-Website aus der Website-Auswahl wurde deaktiviert.
- Fehlerkorrekturen: In Beitragssuchen fehlten manche Ergebnisse. Jetzt funktioniert die Suche wie beabsichtigt!



</de-DE>
<en-US>
14.1:
- Block Editor: a new Shortcode block lets you create and edit shortcodes, we’ve reduced the padding around text-based blocks, and editing very long posts is now a more stable experience.
- Updates: The option to remove a Jetpack site from the site picker has been disabled.
- Bug fixes: searches for posts omitted some results. Now searching works as intended!



</en-US>
<es-ES>
14.1:
- Editor de bloques: un nuevo bloque de shortcode te permite crear y editar shortcodes, hemos reducido el relleno alrededor de los bloques basados en texto y, ahora, la edición de entradas muy largas es una experiencia más estable.
- Actualizaciones: Ha sido desactivada la opción de eliminar un sitio Jetpack del selector de sitios.
- Correcciones de fallos: las búsquedas de entradas omitían algunos resultados. ¡Ahora la búsqueda funciona como debe!


</es-ES>
<fr-CA>
14.1 :
- Éditeur de blocs : un nouveau bloc de code court vous permet de créer et de modifier des codes courts, le remplissage autour des blocs textuels a été réduit et la modification d'articles très longs est désormais plus stable.
- Mises à jour : l’option pour supprimer un site Jetpack du sélecteur de sites a été désactivée.
- Résolution de bugs : les recherches d’articles omettaient certains résultats. La recherche fonctionne désormais correctement.



</fr-CA>
<fr-FR>
14.1 :
- Éditeur de blocs : un nouveau bloc de code court vous permet de créer et de modifier des codes courts, le remplissage autour des blocs textuels a été réduit et la modification d'articles très longs est désormais plus stable.
- Mises à jour : l’option pour supprimer un site Jetpack du sélecteur de sites a été désactivée.
- Résolution de bugs : les recherches d’articles omettaient certains résultats. La recherche fonctionne désormais correctement.



</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
14.1:
- עורך הבלוקים: בלוק השורטקוד החדש מאפשר לך ליצור ולערוך פריטי שורטקוד, צמצמנו את המרווחים מסביב לבלוקים שמבוססים על טקסט והעריכה של פוסטים מאוד ארוכים יציבה יותר כעת.
- עדכונים: האפשרות להסיר אתר של Jetpack מבורר האתרים הושבתה.
- תיקוני באגים: בחיפושים של פוסטים הושמטו כמה תוצאות. כעת החיפוש עובד כשורה!



</iw-IL>
<it-IT>
14.1:
- Editor a blocchi: un nuovo blocco Shortcode ti consente di creare e modificare shortcode, abbiamo ridotto il padding intorno ai blocchi basati sul testo e la modifica di articoli molto lunghi è ora un'esperienza più duratura.
- Aggiornamenti: è stata disabilitata l'opzione per rimuovere un sito Jetpack dal selezionatore di siti.
- Correzioni di bug: la ricerca per articoli ometteva alcuni risultati. Ora funziona come previsto!



</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
14.1:
- ブロックエディター :新しいショートコードブロックで、ショートコードの作成や編集ができます。テキストベースのブロック周囲にあるパディングが削減され、長文の投稿の編集では安定性が向上しました。
- 更新 :サイトピッカーから Jetpack サイトを削除するオプションが無効になりました。
- バグ修正 :投稿の検索で一部の結果が除外されていました。意図したとおりの検索が可能になりました。



</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
14.1:
- 블록 편집기: 새로운 쇼트코드를 사용하여 쇼트코드를 만들고 편집할 수 있습니다. 텍스트 기반 블록 주변의 여백을 줄였으며, 이제 긴 글을 더 안정적인 환경에서 편집할 수 있습니다.
- 업데이트: 사이트 선택기에서 젯팩 사이트를 제거하는 옵션이 비활성화되었습니다.
- 버그 수정: 게시물 검색에서 일부 결과가 생략되었습니다. 이제 검색이 원래대로 작동합니다!



</ko-KR>
<pt-BR>
14.1:
- Editor de blocos: um novo bloco de shortcode permite criar e editar shortcodes, reduzimos o espaço em volta de blocos de texto e melhoramos a estabilidade ao editar posts muito longos.
- Atualização: a opção para remover um site Jetpack do seletor de sites foi desabilitada.
- Correção de erros: pesquisar por posts omitia alguns resultados. Agora a pesquisa funciona como esperado.


</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
14.1:
- Редактор блоков: новый блок шорткодов позволяет создавать и редактировать шорткоды, мы также уменьшили отступы вокруг текстовых блоков. Редактирование очень длинных записей стало более стабильным.
- Возможность удаления сайта с Jetpack из списка сайтов была отключена.
- Исправлен поиск, теперь некоторые результаты поиска более не будут пропущены.


</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
14.1:
- Blockredigeraren: ett nytt kordkodsblock låter dig skapa och redigera kortkoder. Vi har minskat utfyllnaden runt textbaserade block. Nu är upplevelsen stabilare när man redigerar  mycket långa inlägg.
- Uppdateringar: Möjligheten att ta bort Jetpack från webbplatsen har inaktiverats.
- Felrättningar: Vid sökning efter inlägg saknades vissa resultat. Nu fungerar sökningen som det är tänkt!



</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
14.1:
- Blok Düzenleyici: Kısa kodlar oluşturup düzenlemenizi sağlayan yeni bir Kısa Kod bloğu. Metin tabanlı blokların etrafındaki dolguları azalttık ve çok uzun gönderileri düzenlemek artık daha istikrarlı bir deneyim sunuyor.
- Güncelleştirmeler: Site seçiciden bir Jetpack sitesini kaldırma seçeneği devre dışı bırakıldı.
- Hata düzeltmeleri: gönderi aramalarında bazı sonuçlar çıkarıldı. Arama işlevi artık istendiği gibi çalışıyor!



</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
14.1：
- 区块编辑器：新的短代码区块允许您创建和编辑短代码，我们减少了基于文本的区块周围的填充，可以更稳定地编辑非常长的文章。
- 更新：从站点选择器中删除 Jetpack 站点的选项已被禁用。
– 错误修复：搜索文章时忽略了一些结果。现在可以按搜索预期工作！



</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
14.1：
- 區塊編輯器：全新短代碼區塊可讓你建立和編輯短代碼，我們已縮短文字區塊周圍的邊框間距，你現在能夠更穩定地編輯內容很長的文章。
- 更新：從網站選擇器移除 Jetpack 網站的選項已停用。
- 錯誤修正：過去搜尋文章時會省略部分結果。現在搜尋功能已可正常運作！



</zh-TW>
