<ar>
18.1:
-موجز أسبوعي: ملخص للنشاط (المشاهدات والإعجابات والتعليقات) على مواقعك الأكثر استخدامًا يتم إرساله إليك كل يوم اثنين.
-زر تبديل موجود في مكوِّن التضمين لتغيير حجم المحتوى المُضمَّن والإعجاب بمقاطع والفيديو وغيره من الوسائط على الأجهزة الأصغر.
- ميزة تحديد الوقت التي تتيح لك اختيار وقت معين لتلقي تذكير التدوين.
</ar>
<de-DE>
18.1:
- Eine wöchentliche Zusammenfassung: eine Übersicht der Aktivitäten (Aufrufe, Likes, Kommentare) auf deinen meist-genutzten Websites, die dir jeden Montag geschickt wird. 
- Eine Umschaltfunktion im Embed-Block zum Ändern der Inhalte wie Videos und anderen Medien auf kleineren Geräten.
- Ein Zeitauswahlfunktion, mit der du ein bestimmtes Datum und ein Uhrzeit für eine Erinnerung zum Bloggen auswählen kannst.
</de-DE>
<en-US>
18.1:
-A Weekly Roundup: a summary of activity (views, likes, comments) on your most-used sites, sent to you each Monday.
-A toggle option in the Embed block to resize embedded content, like videos and other media, on smaller devices.
-A time selection feature that lets you choose a specific time to receive a Blogging Reminder.
</en-US>
<es-ES>
18.1:
-Un resumen semanal: un resumen de la actividad (vistas, me gusta, comentarios) en tus sitios más usados, que se te envía cada lunes.
-Una opción en el bloque de incrustación para cambiar el tamaño del contenido incrustado, como vídeos y otros medios, en dispositivos más pequeños.
-Una característica de selección de hora que te permite elegir una hora específica para recibir un recordatorio de blogueo.
</es-ES>
<fr-CA>
18.1 :
- Un résumé hebdomadaire : un récapitulatif des activités (vues, mentions J’aime, commentaires) sur vos sites les plus utilisés vous est envoyé tous les lundis.
- Une option de bascule dans le bloc de contenu embarqué pour redimensionner le contenu embarqué, comme les vidéos et autres médias, pour les petits appareils.
- Une fonctionnalité de sélection de l’heure qui vous permet de choisir une heure précise pour recevoir un rappel de blog.
</fr-CA>
<fr-FR>
18.1 :
- Un résumé hebdomadaire : un récapitulatif des activités (vues, mentions J’aime, commentaires) sur vos sites les plus utilisés vous est envoyé tous les lundis.
- Une option de bascule dans le bloc de contenu embarqué pour redimensionner le contenu embarqué, comme les vidéos et autres médias, pour les petits appareils.
- Une fonctionnalité de sélection de l’heure qui vous permet de choisir une heure précise pour recevoir un rappel de blog.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
18.1:
- סיכום שבועי: סיכום של כל הפעילות (צפיות, לייקים, תגובות) באתרים המובילים שלך אשר נשלח בכל יום שני.
- אפשרות לשינוי בבלוק ההטמעה כדי לשנות את גודלו של התוכן המוטמע, כגון סרטונים ופריטי מדיה אחרים, במכשירים קטנים יותר.
- אפשרות לבחירת מועד שמאפשרת לך לבחור מועד ספציפי שבו יישלחו אליך תזכורות לכתיבה בבלוג.
</iw-IL>
<id>
18.1:
- Ringkasan Mingguan: ringkasan aktivitas (tontonan, suka, komentar) di situs Anda yang paling sering digunakan, dikirimkan kepada Anda setiap Senin.
- Pilihan toggle di blok Sematan untuk mengubah ukuran konten yang disematkan, seperti video dan media lain, pada perangkat yang lebih kecil.
- Fitur pemilihan waktu yang mengizinkan Anda memilih waktu tertentu untuk menerima Pengingat Blogging.
</id>
<it-IT>
18.1:
-Un resoconto settimanale: un riepilogo dell'attività (visualizzazioni, Mi piace, commenti) sui tuoi siti più usati, inviato a te ogni lunedì. 
-Un'opzione di attivazione per il blocco Incorporamenti per ridimensionare i contenuti incorporati, come video e altri file multimediali, su dispositivi più piccoli.
-Una funzionalità di selezione dell'orario che ti permette di scegliere un orario specifico per ricevere un Promemoria relativo al blog.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
18.1:
-1週間のまとめ: よく使われているサイトのアクティビティ (表示、いいね、コメント) の要約が毎週月曜日に送信されます。
-埋め込みブロックの切り替えオプション: 小さいデバイスで動画やその他のメディアなどの埋め込みコンテンツをリサイズできます。
-時間選択機能: 特定の時間を選択してブログ投稿のリマインダーを受け取ることができます。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
18.1:
- 주간 총정리: 매주 월요일에 보내드리는 가장 많이 이용한 사이트에 대한 활동(조회수, 좋아요 수, 댓글 수) 요약입니다.
- 비디오 및 기타 미디어 등 소형 기기에 임베드된 콘텐츠의 크기를 조정하는 임베드 블록의 토글 옵션입니다.
- 블로깅 알림을 받을 특정 시간을 선택할 수 있는 시간 선택 기능입니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
18.1:
-Een wekelijkse roundup: een overzicht van activiteit (weergaven, likes, reacties) op je meest gebruikte sites, die elke maandag naar je wordt verzonden.
-Een toggle in het blok Insluiten om het formaat van ingesloten inhoud, zoals video's en andere media, op kleinere apparaten te wijzigen.
-Een tijd selectiefunctie waarmee je een specifiek tijdstip kunt kiezen om een blog herinnering te ontvangen.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
18,1:
- Giro Semanal: toda segunda-feira você recebe um resumo da sua atividade (visualizações, curtidas e comentários) nos sites mais visitados.
- Uma opção nos blocos de mídia incorporada para redimensionar o conteúdo do site para dispositivos menores.
- Uma funcionalidade que deixa você escolher quando quer receber uma notificação do Blogging Reminder.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
18.1:
-Еженедельный обзор: сводка активности (просмотры, отметки "нравится", комментарии) на ваших наиболее часто используемых сайтах, отправляемая вам каждый понедельник.
-Опция переключения в блоке встраивания для изменения размера встроенного содержимого, такого как видео и другие мультимедиа, на небольших устройствах.
-Функция выбора времени, которая позволяет вам выбрать конкретное время для получения напоминания о ведении блога.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
18.1:
-Veckosammanfattning: statistik över aktiviteten (visningar, gillamarkeringar, kommentarer) på dina mest använda webbplatser varje måndag.
-Ett reglage i inbäddningsblocket för att ange om innehållet ska storleksanpassas för mindre skärmar.
-En funktion som låter dig välja vid vilken tid på dagen du vill ha dina bloggningspåminnelser.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
18.1:
-Haftalık Özet: Her Pazartesi en çok kullandığınız sitelerdeki etkinliklerin (görüntülemeler, beğeniler, yorumlar) özeti.
-Daha küçük cihazlarda videolar ve diğer medyalar gibi gömülü içeriği yeniden boyutlandırmak için Gömme blokunda bir geçiş seçeneği.
-Blog Hatırlatıcısı almak için belirli bir zaman seçmenizi sağlayan bir zaman seçme özelliği.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
18.1:
-每周综述：关于你最常用网站的活动（观点、喜好、评论）的总结，每周一发给你。
-“嵌入”区块中的切换选项，用于在较小的设备上调整嵌入内容（如视频和其他媒体）的大小。
-时间选择功能，允许您选择特定的时间来接收博客提醒。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
18.1：
-每週綜合整理：你會在每週一收到最常用網站的活動摘要 (檢視次數、按讚數、留言)。
-嵌入區塊現在可切換調整嵌入內容大小，讓你為較小的裝置調整嵌入影片和其他媒體的大小。
-時間選取功能可讓你指定接收網誌提醒的時間。
</zh-TW>
