<ar>
18.8:
- احصل على اقتراحات الرابط بدلاً من روابط الحافظة المملوءة تلقائيًا الخاصة بمكوِّنات الزر والصورة.
- انقر على "نسخ الرابط" لمشاركة روابط المقالة المنشورة.
- تطابق علامات تبويب قائمة أداة الإدراج لغة جهازك.
- يتم فتح خيارات وسائط الجهاز عند إنشاء مكوِّن المعرض.
- تم حل خطأ حجم الخط والمشكلات المرئية من اليمين إلى اليسار.
- قم بتحرير رابط مكوِّن التضمين في إعدادات المكوِّن.
</ar>
<de-DE>
18.8:
- Erhalte Linkvorschläge anstelle von automatisch ausgefüllten Links aus der Zwischenablage für Buttons und Bildblöcke.
- Klicke auf „Link kopieren“, um Links zu veröffentlichten Beiträgen zu teilen.
- Tabs des Inserter-Menüs stimmen mit der Sprache deines Geräts überein.
- Beim Erstellen eines Galerieblocks werden die Medienoptionen des Geräts geöffnet.
- Problem mit der Schriftgröße und visuelle RTL-Probleme wurden behoben.
- Bearbeite Embed-Block-Links in den Blockeinstellungen.
</de-DE>
<en-US>
18.8:
- Get link suggestions instead of auto-populated clipboard links for Button and Image blocks.
- Click "Copy Link" to share published post links.
- Inserter menu tabs match your device's language.
- Device media options open when creating a Gallery block.
- Font size bug and RTL visual issues are resolved.
- Edit Embed block link in Block Settings.
</en-US>
<fr-CA>
18.8 :
- Recevez des suggestions de liens au lieu des liens du presse-papier remplis autotmatiquement pour les blocs de boutons et d’images.
- Cliquez sur « Copier le lien » pour partager le lien d’articles publiés.
- Inserter menu tabs match your device's language.
- Device media options open when creating a Gallery block.
- Font size bug and RTL visual issues are resolved.
- Edit Embed block link in Block Settings.
</fr-CA>
<fr-FR>
18.8 :
- Recevez des suggestions de liens au lieu des liens du presse-papier remplis autotmatiquement pour les blocs de boutons et d’images.
- Cliquez sur « Copier le lien » pour partager le lien d’articles publiés.
- Inserter menu tabs match your device's language.
- Device media options open when creating a Gallery block.
- Font size bug and RTL visual issues are resolved.
- Edit Embed block link in Block Settings.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
18.8:
- לקבל הצעות לקישורים במקום קישורים של הלוח שהוזנו באופן אוטומטי לבלוק כפתור ולבלוק תמונה.
- ללחוץ על 'להעתיק את הקישור' כדי לשתף קישורים לפוסטים שפורסמו.
-הלשוניות בתפריט המוסיף תואמות לשפה במכשיר שלך.
- אפשרויות המדיה במכשיר נפתחות כאשר יוצרים בלוק גלריה.
- תיקנו באג שגרם לבעיות בגודל הגופן ובעיות בכיווניות מימין לשמאל.
- לערוך קישור בבלוק ההטמעה דרך הגדרות הבלוק.
</iw-IL>
<id>
18.8:
- Dapatkan saran tautan alih-alih tautan papan klip yang terisi otomatis untuk blok Tombol dan Gambar.
- Klik "Salin Tautan" untuk membagikan tautan pos yang telah diposkan.
- Tab menu penyisip sesuai dengan bahasa perangkat Anda.
- Pilihan media perangkat terbuka saat membuat blok Galeri.
- Masalah bug ukuran font dan tampilan RTL telah diperbaiki.
- Mengedit tautan blok Sematan di Pengaturan Blok.
</id>
<ja-JP>
18.8:
- ボタンブロックと画像ブロックのクリップボードリンクが自動入力される代わりに、リンク候補が表示されます。
- 「リンクをコピー」をクリックすると、公開した投稿のリンクが共有されます。
- 挿入メニューのタブは端末の言語と一致します。
- ギャラリーブロックの作成時に端末のメディア設定が開きます。
- フォントサイズのバグと RTL の視覚的な問題が解決されました。
- ブロック設定で埋め込みブロックのリンクを編集します。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
18.8:
- 버튼 및 이미지 블록의 자동으로 채워지는 클립보드 링크 대신에 링크 제안을 이용하세요.
- 발행한 글 링크를 공유하려면 "링크 복사"를 클릭하세요.
- 삽입기 메뉴 탭이 기기의 언어와 일치합니다.
- 갤러리 블록을 만들 때 기기 미디어 옵션이 열립니다.
- 글꼴 크기 버그와 RTL 비주얼 문제가 해결되었습니다.
- 블록 설정에서 임베드 블록을 편집하세요.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
18.8:
- Ontvang link suggesties in plaats van automatisch ingevulde klembord links voor knop- en afbeeldingsblokken.
- Klik op "Link kopiëren" om gepubliceerde bericht links te delen.
- Inserter menu tabs komen overeen met de taal van je apparaat.
- Apparaat media-opties worden geopend bij het maken van een galerijblok.
- Lettertypegrootte bug en RTL visuele problemen zijn opgelost.
- Bewerk de insluitblok link in Blok instellingen.
</nl-NL>
<ru-RU>
18.8:
- Вместо автоматического заполнения из буфера, вы получите предложения для ссылок в блоках "Кнопка" и "Изображение"
- Нажмите «Копировать ссылку», чтобы делиться ссылками на опубликованные записи.
- Вкладки меню вставки теперь соответствуют языку вашего устройства.
- Параметры мультимедиа для устройства открываются при создании блока галереи.
- Исправлена ​​ошибка размера шрифта и визуальные проблемы RTL.
- Редактирование ссылки в блоке вставки перенесено в настройки блока.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
18.8:
- Få länkförslag istället för automatiskt ifyllda urklippslänkar för knapp- och bildblock.
- Klicka på "Kopiera länk" för att dela publicerade inläggslänkar.
- Infogarmenyns flikar matchar din enhets språk.
- Enhetens mediaalternativ öppnas när du skapar ett galleriblock.
- Textstorleksfel och visuella RTL-fel har åtgärdats.
- Redigera länk för inbäddningsblock i blockinställningarna.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
18.8:
- Düğme ve Görüntü blokları için otomatik olarak doldurulan pano bağlantıları yerine bağlantı önerileri alın. 
- Yayınlanan gönderi bağlantılarını paylaşmak için "Bağlantıyı Kopyala"ya tıklayın.
- Ekleyici menü sekmeleri cihazınızın diliyle eşleşir.
- Bir Galeri bloku oluştururken cihaz medya seçenekleri açılır.
- Yazı tipi boyutu hatası ve Görsel RTL sorunları çözüldü.
- Blok Ayarları'ndan Gömülü blok bağlantısını düzenleyin.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
18.8：
- 获取按钮和图像区块的链接建议，而不是自动填充的剪贴板链接。
- 点击“复制链接”，分享已发布文章的链接。
- 插入器菜单选项卡与您的设备语言相对应。
- 设备媒体选项在创建图库区块时打开。
- 字体大小错误和 RTL 视觉问题已解决。
- 在”区块设置“中编辑嵌入区块链接。
</zh-CN>
