<ar>
13.0:
* تحسينات مُحرّر المكوّنات: يتم تمكين المحرر تلقائيًا عند فتح مقالة مكوّن (إلا إذا قمت بالإلغاء في الإصدار 12.9)، أو يمكنك تمكينه على أساس كل موقع.
* تحسينات إمكانية الوصول: يمكن الآن لقرّاء الشاشة قراءة المزيد بشاشة الإحصائيات.
* تحسينات عامة لقابلية الاستخدام: تسجيل الدخول أسرع، والألوان أكثر تناسقًا عبر الشاشات، وإصلاح الأخطاء ووضع حد لبعض الأعطال.
</ar>
<de-DE>
13.0:
* Verbesserungen am Block-Editor: Der Editor wird automatisch aktiviert, wenn du einen Blockbeitrag öffnest (wenn du dies nicht in Version 12.9 deaktiviert hast), oder du kannst ihn für jede einzelne Website aktivieren.
* Verbesserungen der Bedienungshilfen: Screenreader können jetzt mehr Inhalte des Statistikbildschirms erkennen.
* Allgemeine Verbesserungen der Benutzerfreundlichkeit: Die Anmeldung funktioniert schneller, die Farben sind konsistenter auf allen Bildschirmen und Fehlerbehebungen beseitigen die Ursachen einiger Abstürze.
</de-DE>
<en-US>
13.0:
* Block editor improvements: the editor is auto-enabled when you open a block post (unless you opted out in v12.9), or you can enable it on a per-site basis.
* Accessibility improvements: screen readers can now read more of the stats screen.
* General usability improvements: logging in is speedier, colors are more consistent across screens, and bug fixes put an end to some crashes.
</en-US>
<es-ES>
13.0
* Mejoras en el editor de bloques: el editor se activa automáticamente cuando abres un bloque de entradas (salvo que lo hayas desactivado en la versión 12.9) o puedes activarlo en base a cada sitio.
*Mejoras de accesibilidad: los lectores de pantalla ahora pueden leer mejor la pantalla de estadísticas.
* Mejoras de uso general: el acceso es rapidísimo, los colores son más consistentes entre pantallas y las correcciones de fallos ponen fin a algunos errores.
</es-ES>
<fr-CA>
13.0 :
* Améliorations de l'éditeur de blocs : l'éditeur est automatiquement activé lorsque vous ouvrez un bloc article (à moins que vous n’ayez décidé du contraire lors de la v12.9) ou vous pouvez l'activer sur une base par site.
* Améliorations de l'accessibilité : les lecteurs d'écran peuvent désormais lire davantage de l'écran de statistiques.
* Améliorations de l'ergonomie générale : la connexion est plus rapide, les couleurs sont plus uniformes d'un écran à l’autre et les corrections de bug ont mis fin à certains plantages.
</fr-CA>
<fr-FR>
13.0 :
* Améliorations de l'éditeur de blocs : l'éditeur est automatiquement activé lorsque vous ouvrez un bloc article (à moins que vous n’ayez décidé du contraire lors de la v12.9) ou vous pouvez l'activer sur une base par site.
* Améliorations de l'accessibilité : les lecteurs d'écran peuvent désormais lire davantage de l'écran de statistiques.
* Améliorations de l'ergonomie générale : la connexion est plus rapide, les couleurs sont plus uniformes d'un écran à l’autre et les corrections de bug ont mis fin à certains plantages.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
13.0:
* שיפורים בעורך הבלוקים: העורך מופעל באופן אוטומטי כאשר פותחים פוסט עם בלוק (אלא אם עזבת בגרסה 12.9) ואפשר גם להגדיר את ההפעלה שלו לכל אתר בנפרד.
* שיפורים בנגישות: קוראי מסך יכולים כעת לקרוא פרטים נוספים במסך של הנתונים הסטטיסטיים.
* שיפורים כלליים בשימושיות: ההתחברות מהירה יותר, הצבעים אחידים יותר במסכים השונים ותיקנו כמה באגים שגרמו לקריסות.
</iw-IL>
<id>
13.0:
* Peningkatan penyunting blok: penyunting diaktifkan otomatis saat Anda membuka pos blok (kecuali Anda tidak memilihnya di v12.9), atau Anda dapat mengaktifkannya untuk setiap situs.
* Peningkatan aksesibilitas: pembaca layar kini dapat membaca lebih banyak layar statistik.
* Peningkatan kegunaan umum: login lebih cepat, warna lebih konsisten antarlayar, dan perbaikan bug mengakhiri sejumlah masalah crash.
</id>
<it-IT>
13.0:
* Miglioramenti all'editor dei blocchi: l'editor viene abilitato automaticamente quando si apre un articolo a blocchi (salvo disattivazione nella versione v12.9). In alternativa è possibile abilitarlo su singoli siti.
* Miglioramenti dell'accessibilità: i lettori di schermo possono ora leggere una maggiore quantità della schermata delle statistiche.
* Miglioramenti della fruibilità generale: l'accesso è più veloce, i colori sono più coerenti tra le diverse schermate e la correzione di alcuni errori ha eliminato alcuni arresti anomali.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
13.0:
* ブロックエディターの改善 :ブロック投稿を開くと、エディターが自動的に有効になります (v12.9でオプトアウトした場合を除く)。サイトごとに有効にすることもできます。
* アクセシビリティの改善 :スクリーンリーダーで、より多くの統計画面を読み込めるようになりました。
* 一般的なユーザビリティの向上 :ログインが迅速化され、画面全体の色の一貫性が向上し、バグの修正により一部のクラッシュが解消されました。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
13.0:
* 블록 편집기 개선 사항: 블록 글을 열 때(v12.9에서 옵트아웃하지 않은 경우) 편집기가 자동으로 활성화되거나 사이트별로 활성화할 수 있습니다.
* 접근성 개선 사항: 이제 화면 판독기에서 더 많은 통계 화면을 읽을 수 있습니다.
* 일반적인 유용성 개선 사항: 로그인 속도가 빨라지고 화면 전체 색상의 일관성이 높아졌으며 버그 수정 덕분에 일부 충돌이 더 이상 발생하지 않습니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
13.0:
* Verbeteringen aan de blok-editor: De editor is automatisch ingeschakeld als je een blokbericht opent (tenzij je je hebt uitgeschreven in v12.9), of je kunt het per site inschakelen.
* Verbeteringen aan de toegankelijkheid: Schermlezers kunnen nu meer zien van het statistiekenscherm.
* algemene verbeteringen voor gebruik Inloggen gaat sneller, kleuren zijn consistenter over de schermen verdeeld, en bugfixes hebben sommige crashes beëindigd.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
13.0:
* Melhorias no editor de blocos: o editor é aberto automaticamente ao abrir um post com blocos (a menos que você tenha desativado isso na versão 12.9). Você também pode configurar o editor por site.
* Melhorias de acessibilidade: agora leitores de tela podem ler mais informações em estatísticas.
* Melhorias gerais: acessar o aplicativo agora é mais rápido, atualizamos as cores para ter mais consistência e corrigimos erros que causavam falhas no aplicativo.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
13.0:
* Улучшения в редакторе блоков: при открытии записи с блоками редактор блоков будет включен автоматически (если только вы не отказались в версии 12.9), вы также можете включить его для отдельных сайтов.
* Улучшения доступности: программы чтения с экрана теперь могут прочесть больше с экрана статистики.
* Общие улучшения использования: вход теперь работает быстрее, цветовая схема более целостна при переходе между экранами, исправления ошибок приводящих к падению приложения.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
13.0:
* Förbättringar i blockredigeraren: redigeraren aktiveras automatiskt när du öppnar ett inlägg som använder block (om du inte stängde av detta i version 12.9). Du kan ocks[ aktivera detta för vissa webbplatser.
* Tillgänglighetsförbättringar: nu kan skärmläsare läsa mer av informationen i statistikvyn.
* Allmänna användbarhetsförbättringar: inloggning går snabbare, färgerna stämmer bättre överens mellan olika vyer och några felrättningar har satt stopp för ett antal situationer med programkrascher.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
13.0:
* Blok düzenleyici iyileştirmeleri: Düzenleyici, bir blok gönderisini açtığınızda otomatik olarak etkinleştirilebilir (12.9 sürümünde hizmeti kapatmadıysanız) veya bunu site bazında etkinleştirebilirsiniz.
* Erişilebilirlik iyileştirmeleri: Ekran okuyucular artık istatistik ekranından daha fazla içerik okuyabiliyor.
* Genel kullanılabilirlik iyileştirmeleri: Oturum açma işlemi daha hızlı, renkler ekranlarda daha tutarlı ve hata düzeltmeleri bazı kilitlenmeleri giderdi.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
13.0：
* 区块编辑器改进：当您打开一篇区块文章时，编辑器会自动启用（除非您选择退出 v12.9）。您还可以根据每个站点启用它。
* 访问方面的改进：屏幕阅读器现在可以阅读统计数据屏幕中的更多信息。
* 通用性方面的改进：登录速度更快，屏幕颜色更一致，错误修复解决了一些崩溃问题。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
13.0：
* 改善區塊編輯器：編輯器會在你開啟區塊文章 (除非你選擇退出 v12.9) 時自動啟用，你也可以為每個網站啟用編輯器。
* 改善協助工具：螢幕閱讀器現在可以讀取更多統計資料畫面。
* 改善一般可用性：登入更快速、色彩在螢幕顯示上更一致，且部分當機錯誤也已修正。
</zh-TW>
