<ar>
16.2:
تحسينات محرِّر المكوّن: لقد قمنا بتحسين الأداء العام والسرعة، والذي قد تلاحظه عند فتح المحرِّر لإنشاء مقالة جديدة. لقد قمنا أيضًا بتحسين مكوّن الصورة، مع دعم أفضل لتحميل صور متعددة.

تحديثات وإصلاحات أخرى: يستخدم تطبيقك الآن منتقي وسائط جديدًا عند تحديد ملفات للمقالات وأيقونة موقعك وصورتك الرمزية وغيرها من الأماكن الأخرى. لقد أصلحنا أيضًا خطأً في مواقع مستضافة ذاتيًا خالصة على HTTP الذي منع الصور المميزة من الظهور في قائمة المقالات.

</ar>
<de-DE>
16.2:
Block-Editor: Wir haben die allgemeine Performance verbessert, was dir vielleicht auffallen wird, wenn du das nächste Mal einen Beitrag beginnst. Der Bildblock verfügt nun über besseren Support beim Hochladen mehrerer Bilder.

Weitere Updates: Deine App nutzt beim Auswählen der Dateien eine neue Medienauswahl.  Wir haben auch einen Bug auf den rein selbstverwalteten Websites auf HTTP beseitigt, der sich negativ auf die Beitragsbilder in den Beitragslisten ausgewirkt hat.
</de-DE>
<en-US>
16.2:
Block editor enhancements: We’ve improved the overall performance and speed, which you might notice when you open the editor to create a new post. We’ve also improved the Image block, with better support for uploading multiple images.

Other updates and fixes: Your app now uses a new Media Picker when you select files for posts, your site icon, Gravatar, and other places. We also fixed a bug on pure self-hosted sites on HTTP that prevented featured images from displaying in the Posts List.

</en-US>
<es-ES>
16.2:
Editor de bloques: Hemos mejorado el rendimiento general, que podrás notar al iniciar una nueva entrada. El bloque de imágenes ahora tiene mejor compatibilidad para subir múltiples imágenes.

Más actualizaciones: Tu aplicación usa un nuevo selector de medios cuando seleccionas archivos. También hemos corregido un fallo en los sitios autoalojados en HTTP puro que afectaba a las imágenes destacadas en la lista de entradas.
</es-ES>
<fr-CA>
16.2 :
Éditeur de blocs : nous avons amélioré les performances globales. Vous le remarquerez lorsque vous créerez un article. Le bloc Image offre désormais une meilleure prise en charge pour le chargement de plusieurs images.

Plus de mises à jour : votre application utilise un nouveau sélecteur de média lorsque vous sélectionnez des fichiers. Nous avons également résolu un bug au niveau des sites auto-hébergés en HTTP, qui concernait les images mises en avant dans la Liste d’articles.
</fr-CA>
<fr-FR>
16.2 :
Éditeur de blocs : nous avons amélioré les performances globales. Vous le remarquerez lorsque vous créerez un article. Le bloc Image offre désormais une meilleure prise en charge pour le chargement de plusieurs images.

Plus de mises à jour : votre application utilise un nouveau sélecteur de média lorsque vous sélectionnez des fichiers. Nous avons également résolu un bug au niveau des sites auto-hébergés en HTTP, qui concernait les images mises en avant dans la Liste d’articles.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
16.2:
עורך הבלוקים: שיפרנו את הביצועים באופן כללי, כפי שאפשר לראות כשיוצרים פוסט חדש. שיפרנו גם את בלוק התמונה עם תמיכה טובה יותר בהעלאה של מספר תמונות במקביל.

עדכונים ותיקונים נוספים: הוספנו לאפליקציה בורר מדיה חדש לבחירת קבצים לפוסטים, לסמל האתר שלך, ל-Gravatar ולמיקומים אחרים. כמו כן תיקנו באג באתרים באחסון עצמי ב-HTTP שמנע תצוגה של תמונות מרכזיות ברשימת הפוסטים.

</iw-IL>
<in>
16.2:
Editor blok: Kami telah meningkatkan performa secara keseluruhan, yang mungkin dapat Anda rasakan saat mulai membuat pos baru. Sekarang blok Gambar memiliki dukungan lebih baik untuk mengunggah gambar dalam jumlah banyak. 

Pembaruan lainnya: Aplikasi Anda menggunakan Pemilih Media baru saat Anda memilih file. Kami juga memperbaiki bug pada situs hosting sendiri di HTTP yang memengaruhi gambar andalan pada Daftar Pos.
</in>
<it-IT>
16.2:
Editor a blocchi: Abbiamo migliorato le prestazioni complessive, cosa che puoi notare quando avvii un nuovo post. Il blocco Immagine ora ha un migliore supporto per il caricamento di più immagini.

Altri aggiornamenti: La tua app utilizza un nuovo selezionatore di contenuti quando selezioni i file. Abbiamo anche corretto un bug sui siti ospitati personalmente puri su HTTP che interessava le immagini in evidenza nell'elenco degli articoli.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
16.2 : 
ブロックエディターの向上 : 全体的なパフォーマンスと速度を向上しました。これは、エディターを開いて新しい投稿を開始するときに気づくかもしれません。 また、画像ブロックでの複数の画像のアップロードのサポートを強化しました。

その他の更新と修正 : アプリで、投稿、ファビコン、Gravatar などの場所でファイルを選択する際に、新しいメディア選択ツールが使用されるようになりました。 また、投稿リストのアイキャッチ画像が表示されない原因となっていた、HTTP 上の純インストール型のサイトの問題を修正しました。

</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
16.2:
블록 편집기 개선: 전체적으로 성능과 속도를 개선했어요. 새 글을 만들기 위해 편집기를 열면 알림을 받을 수 있어요. 다중 이미지 업로드를 더 잘 지원하도록 이미지 블록을 개선했어요.

다른 업데이트와 수정: 이제 앱은 글, 아이콘, 그라바타, 그리고 다른 장소에 사용할 파일을 선택할 때, 새 미디어 선택기를 사용해요. 또한 온전한 자체 호스팅 사이트에서 글록목에 보이는 대표 이미지를 방해하는 HTTP의 버그도 역시 수정했어요.

</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
16.2:
Blok-editor: we hebben de algehele prestaties verbeterd, wat je wellicht merkt wanneer je een nieuw bericht start. Het afbeeldingsblok heeft nu betere ondersteuning voor het uploaden van meerdere afbeeldingen.

Meer updates: je app gebruikt een nieuwe mediakiezer wanneer je bestanden selecteert. We hebben ook een bug gerepareerd op puur door jezelf gehoste sites op HTTP die de uitgelichte afbeeldingen in de berichtenlijst beïnvloedde.
</nl-NL>
<ru-RU>
16.2:
Редактор блоков: Улучшения производительности, особенно при создании новой записи. Улучшен блок изображения, лучшая поддержка загрузки множественных изображений

Другое: Использование нового инстремента выбора медиафайлов для записей, значка сайта, Gravatar и др. Исправлена ошибка для самостоятельно размещенных сайтов с HTTP, изображение записи не показывалось в списке записей.


</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
16.2:
Förbättringar i blockredigeraren: Högre prestanda överlag. Det märker du när du skapar ett nytt inlägg. Vi har även förbättrat bildblocket, med bättre stöd för uppladdning av flera bilder åt gången.

Andra förbättringar och rättelser: Appen använder en ny mediaväljare när du väljer filer för inlägg, webbplatsikon, Gravatar m.m. Vi har också rättat ett fel för webbplatser på webbhotell med HTTP där utvalda bilder inte visades i inläggslistan.

</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
16.2:
Blok düzenleyici: Yeni bir gönderi başlattığınızda fark edebileceğiniz gibi genel performans iyileştirildi.  Görüntü bloğu artık birden çok görüntüyü yüklemek için daha iyi desteğe sahip.

Daha fazla güncelleme: Dosya seçerken artık uygulamanızda yeni bir Medya Seçici kullanılıyor. Ayrıca, HTTP üzerinde tamamen kendi kendine barındırılan sitelerde, öne çıkan görsellerin Yayınlar Listesinde görüntülenmesini engelleyen bir hata düzeltildi.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
16.2：区块编辑器的增强功能：我们提高了整体性能和速度，当您打开编辑器创建新帖子时，您可能会注意到。我们还改进了“图片”区块，并更好地支持上传多张图片。其他更新和修复：现在，当您选择用于文章，网站图标，Gravatar和其他位置的文件时，您的应用程序将使用新的媒体选择器。我们还修复了HTTP上纯自托管网站上的错误，该错误使特色图片无法显示在文章列表中。

</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
16.2：
區塊編輯器增強功能：我們已提高整體效能和速度，當你開啟編輯器撰寫新文章時，可能就會注意到這點。 我們也改善了圖片區塊，現在提供上傳多個圖片的支援。

其他更新和修正：現在為文章、網站圖示、Gravatar 和其他地方選擇檔案時，應用程式將使用新的媒體選擇器。 我們也修正了 HTTP 上純自助託管網站出現的錯誤，文章清單中的特色圖片不會再無法顯示。

</zh-TW>
