<ar>
16.3:
يسعدنا الإعلان عن العديد من الميزات الجديدة لتطبيق ووردبريس على الهاتف المحمول ألا وهي:
- عروض شرائح بوضع ملء الشاشة للصور أو مقاطع الفيديو لمواقع WP.com و Jetpack؛
- والخيار لاختيار تصميم الصفحة الرئيسية عند إنشاء موقع WP.com؛
- وظائف محسَّنة لتعيين أبعاد الغلاف والأعمدة؛
- وزر المتابعة / إلغاء المتابعة لقسم تعليقات الموقع، ما يسمح للمستخدمين بتعقٌّب محادثة ما وإخطارهم بالتحديثات عبر البريد الإلكتروني (غير مدعوم للمواقع المستضافة ذاتيًا غير المتصلة بـ Jetpack).
</ar>
<de-DE>
16.3:
Wir freuen uns sehr, mehrere neue Funktionen für die WordPress-Mobil-App vorzustellen:
- Vollbild-Diashows von Fotos oder Videos für WP.com- und Jetpack-Websites;
- Die Option, bei Erstellung einer WP.com-Website ein Design für die Startseite auszuwählen;
- Und einen Button zum Folgen/Nicht mehr folgen für die Kommentarfunktion einer Website (nicht unterstützt für selbst gehostete Websites, die nicht mit Jetpack verbunden sind).
</de-DE>
<en-US>
16.3:
We’re pleased to announce several new WordPress mobile app features:
- full-screen slideshows of photos or videos for WP.com and Jetpack sites;
- the option to pick a homepage design when creating a WP.com site;
- improved functionality for setting the dimensions of Cover and Columns;
- and a Follow/Unfollow button for a site’s comments section, allowing users to track a conversation and be notified by email of updates (not supported for self-hosted sites that aren’t connected to Jetpack).
</en-US>
<es-ES>
16.3:
Estamos encantados de anunciar varias nuevas características de la aplicación móvil para WordPress:
- Presentaciones de diapositivas a pantalla completa de fotos o vídeos para los sitios de WP.com y Jetpack;
- La opción para elegir un diseño de página de inicio al crear un sitio en WP.com;
- Y un botón par seguir/dejar de seguir para la sección de comentarios de un sitio (no compatible con los sitios autoalojados que no estén conectados a Jetpack).
</es-ES>
<fr-CA>
16.3 :
Nous sommes heureux d’annoncer l’ajout de plusieurs nouvelles fonctionnalités à l’application mobile WordPress :
- diaporama photos ou vidéo en plein écran pour les sites WP.com et Jetpack ;
- possibilité de choisir le design d’une page d’accueil lors de la création d’un site WP.com ;
- bouton S’abonner/Se désabonner de la section Commentaires d’un site (non pris en charge pour les sites auto-hébergés non connectés à Jetpack).
</fr-CA>
<fr-FR>
16.3 :
Nous sommes heureux d’annoncer l’ajout de plusieurs nouvelles fonctionnalités à l’application mobile WordPress :
- diaporama photos ou vidéo en plein écran pour les sites WP.com et Jetpack ;
- possibilité de choisir le design d’une page d’accueil lors de la création d’un site WP.com ;
- bouton S’abonner/Se désabonner de la section Commentaires d’un site (non pris en charge pour les sites auto-hébergés non connectés à Jetpack).
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
16.3:
אנחנו שמחים להכריז על כמה אפשרויות חדשות באפליקציה לנייד של WordPress:
- מצגות במסך מלא של תמונות או סרטונים באתרים של WP.com ושל Jetpack;
- האפשרות לבחור עיצוב לעמוד הבית כאשר יוצרים אתר WP.com;
- פונקציונליות משופרת בהגדרת הממדים של הכיסוי והטורים;
- וכפתור 'לעקוב/לבטל מעקב' במקטע התגובות של האתר כדי לאפשר למשתמשים לעקוב אחר השיחה ולקבל עדכונים באימייל (לא נתמך באתרים באחסון עצמי שלא מחוברים אל Jetpack).
</iw-IL>
<in>
16.3:
Dengan gembira kami umumkan beberapa fitur baru aplikasi seluler WordPress:
- slideshow foto atau video layar penuh untuk WP.com dan situs Jetpack;
- opsi desain halaman saat membuat situs WP.com;
- dan tombol Ikuti/Batal Mengikuti untuk bagian komentar situs (tidak didukung untuk situs hosting sendiri yang tidak terhubung ke Jetpack).
</in>
<ja-JP>
16.3:
WordPress モバイルアプリの新しい機能をお知らせします。
- WP.com および Jetpack サイトの写真または動画のフルスクリーンスライドショー
- WP.com サイトの作成時にホームページのデザインを選択するオプション
- カバーと列のサイズを設定する機能の改善
- サイトのコメントセクションのフォロー/フォロー解除ボタンで、ユーザーは会話の追跡や更新情報のメール通知が可能に (Jetpack に接続されていないインストール型のサイトはサポートされていません)。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
16.3:
새 워드프레스 모바일 앱 기능을 알리게되어 기쁩니다:
- WP.com과 젯팩 사이트에 대한 사진이나 비디오의 전체화면 슬라이드쇼;
- WP.com 사이트를 만들 때 홈페이지 디자인을 선택할 수 있는 옵션;
- 표지나 컬럼의 크기를 설정하기 위한 기능을 개선;
- 그리고 이용자가 대화를 추적하고 업데이트 이메일로 알림을 받을 수 있는, 사이트 댓글 구역에 대한 팔로우/언팔로우 버튼 (젯팩을 연결하지 않은 자체 호스팅에는 지원하지 않습니다).
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
16.3:
We zijn verheugd verschillende nieuwe functies van de mobiele WordPress app aan te kondigen:
- slide-voorstellingen op volledig scherm van foto's of video's voor WP.com en Jetpack sites;
- de optie om een homepage-ontwerp te kiezen bij het maken van een WP.com site;
- en een knop Volgen/Ontvolgen voor de reacties sectie van een site (niet ondersteund voor door jezelf gehoste sites die niet zijn verbonden met Jetpack).
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
16.3:
Estamos felizes em anunciar diversos novos recursos no aplicativo WordPress:
- slideshow em tela cheia de fotos ou vídeos de sites do WP.com e Jetpack;
- possibilidade de selecionar um modelo para a página inicial ao criar um site no WP.com;
- e um botão para seguir ou parar de seguir comentários em sites (não é suportado em sites auto-hospedados não conectados ao Jetpack).
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
16.3:
Мы рады объявить о нескольких новых функциях мобильного приложения WordPress:
- полноэкранные слайд-шоу из фото или видео для сайтов WP.com и Jetpack;
- возможность выбрать дизайн домашней страницы при создании сайта WP.com;
- улучшен функционал настройки размеров обложки и столбцов;
- кнопка "Подписаться / отменить подписку" для комментариев сайта, позволяющая пользователям отслеживать беседу и получать уведомления  по электронной почте (для автономных сайтов требуется Jetpack).
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
16.3:
Vi har glädjen att presentera en rad nya funktioner i WordPress mobilapp:
- fullskärms bildspel med foton och video för webbplatser hos WP.com de med Jetpack,
- möjlighet att välja startsidesdesign när du skapar en webbplats hos WP.com,
- och en knapp för att följa och sluta följa kommentarsektionen på en webbplats (stöds inte för webbplats på egen server/webbhotell om den inte är ansluten till Jetpack).
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
16.3:
Bir kaç yeni WordPress mobil uygulama özelliğini bildirmekten mutluluk duyuyoruz:
- WP.com ve Jetpack siteleri için tam ekran fotoğraf ve video slayt gösterileri;
- bir WP.com sitesi oluştururken ana sayfa tasarımı seçme seçeneği;
- ve sitenin yorumlar bölümü için, kullanıcıların sohbeti takip edebildikleri ve e-posta ile bildirim alabildikleri bir takip et/takipten çık düğmesi (Jetpack bağlantısı olmayan özel barındırma sunucularında desteklenmiyor.)
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
16.3：
我们非常高兴宣布 WordPress 移动应用程序推出了几项新功能：
- WP.com 和 Jetpack 网站可以全屏播放照片或视频幻灯片；
- 创建 WP.com 站点时可以选择主页设计；
- 改进了封面和栏目尺寸的设置功能；-
 以及网站评论部分的“关注/取消关注”按钮，让用户可以跟踪对话并通过电子邮件接收更新通知（未关联至 Jetpack 的自托管网站不支持）。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
16.3：
很高興在此宣佈幾項 WordPress 行動應用程式全新功能：
- WP.com 和 Jetpack 網站的全螢幕相片或影片投影片功能；
- 建立 WP.com 網站時可選擇是否挑選首頁設計；
改善封面和欄位尺寸的設定功能；
- 另外，網站留言區段新增「追蹤/停止追蹤」按鈕，讓使用者能夠追蹤討論情況，並接收更新電子郵件通知 (不支援未連結 Jetpack 的自助託管網站)。
</zh-TW>
