<ar>
13.4:
* تمت إضافة دعم المعاينة عن بُعد للمقالات والصفحات.
* تظل المقالات الموضوعة في سلة المهملات في سلة المهملات. لا بد من استعادتها قبل التحرير أو المعاينة.
* تم إصلاح ما يلي: يؤدي النقر على "نشر" حول مقالة خاصة إلى نشر مقالتك بشكل موثوق الآن على أنها خاصة، وتم حل بعض مشكلات تحرير الرابط.
* تُنسخ التغييرات غير المحفوظة على المقالات والصفحات نسخًا احتياطيًا تلقائيًا.
</ar>
<de-DE>
13.4:
* Die externe Vorschau wird nun für Beiträge und Seiten unterstützt.
* In den Papierkorb verschobene Beiträge bleiben dort. Zur Bearbeitung oder Ansicht einer Vorschau müssen sie zuerst wiederhergestellt werden.
* Behoben: Durch Klicken auf „Veröffentlichen“ bei einem privaten Beitrag wird der Beitrag nun zuverlässig privat veröffentlicht. Dabei wurden Probleme bei der Linkbearbeitung gelöst.
* Nicht gespeicherte Änderungen an Beiträgen und Seiten werden automatisch gesichert.
</de-DE>
<en-US>
13.4:
* Added Remote Preview support for posts and pages.
* Trashed posts stay trashed. They must be restored before editing or previewing.
* Fixed: Clicking on “Publish” on a private post now reliably publishes the post as private, some link editing issues resolved.
* Unsaved changes to posts and pages are automatically backed up.
</en-US>
<es-ES>
13.4:
* Añadida compatibilidad de vista previa remota para entradas y páginas.
* Las entradas de la papelera se quedan en la papelera. Deben ser restauradas antes de editar o previsualizar.
* Corregido: Ahora, al hacer clic en «Publicar» en una entrada privada, la entrada se publica con seguridad como privada; resueltos algunos problemas de edición de enlaces.
* Los cambios no guardados en entradas y páginas se guardan automáticamente en una copia de seguridad.
</es-ES>
<fr-CA>
13.4 :
* Ajout de la prévisualisation à distance pour les publications et les pages.
*Les publications mises à la poubelle restent à la poubelle. Elles doivent être restaurées avant de les modifier ou de les prévisualiser.
* Corrigé : Le fait de cliquer "Publier" sur une publication privée la publier effectivement de manière privée, et certains problèmes de modification de liens ont été résolus.
* Les modifications non sauvegardées des publications et des pages sont automatiquement sauvegardées.
</fr-CA>
<fr-FR>
13.4 :
* Ajout de la prévisualisation à distance pour les publications et les pages.
*Les publications mises à la poubelle restent à la poubelle. Elles doivent être restaurées avant de les modifier ou de les prévisualiser.
* Corrigé : Le fait de cliquer "Publier" sur une publication privée la publier effectivement de manière privée, et certains problèmes de modification de liens ont été résolus.
* Les modifications non sauvegardées des publications et des pages sont automatiquement sauvegardées.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
13.4:
- הוספנו תמיכה בתצוגה מקדימה בעמדות עבודה מרוחקות לפוסטים ולעמודים.
* פוסטים שהועברו לפח נשארים בפח. עליך לשחזר את הפריטים לפני עריכה או יצירה של תצוגה מקדימה.
* בעיות שתוקנו: לחיצה על "פרסום" בפוסט פרטי כעת מפרסמת באופן מהימן את הפוסט כפרטי. בנוסף, תיקנו כמה מהבעיות בעריכת הקישורים.
* שינויים שלא נשמרו לפוסטים ולעמודים מגובים באופן אוטומטי.
</iw-IL>
<id>
13.4:
* Menambahkan dukungan Pratinjau Jarak Jauh untuk pos dan halaman.
* Pos yang dibuang tetap ada di sampah. Pos tersebut harus dipulihkan untuk dapat disunting atau dipratinjau.
* Perbaikan: Mengklik “Publikasikan” pada pos pribadi kini secara akurat memublikasikan pos sebagai pribadi, beberapa masalah penyuntingan tautan telah diperbaiki.
* Perubahan yang tidak tersimpan pada pos dan halaman akan otomatis dicadangkan.
</id>
<it-IT>
13.4:
* Aggiunto supporto per l'anteprima da remoto per articoli e pagine.
* Gli articoli nel cestino restano nel cestino. Devono essere ripristinati prima della modifica o dell'anteprima.
* Correzione: facendo clic su "Pubblica" su un articolo privato, ora l'articolo viene correttamente pubblicato come privato; risolti alcuni problemi di modifica dei link.
* Backup automatico delle modifiche non salvate ad articoli e pagine.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
13.4:
* 投稿とページの「リモートプレビュー」サポートを追加しました。
* ゴミ箱に移動済みの投稿は、そのままゴミ箱に残ります。編集したり、プレビューするには、元に戻す必要があります。
* 修正済み事項として、非公開の投稿の「公開」をクリックすることによって、投稿を確実に非公開で公開できるようになりました。リンク編集に関するいくつかの問題を解消しました。
* 投稿とページの保存されていない変更を自動的にバックアップします。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
13.4:
* 글 및 페이지에 대한 원격 미리보기 지원이 추가되었습니다.
* 휴지통으로 이동한 글은 계속 휴지통에 있습니다. 편집 또는 미리보기 전에 복원해야 합니다.
* 수정 사항: 이제 비공개 글에서 “발행”을 클릭하면 글이 안정적으로 비공개로 발행되고, 일부 링크 편집 문제가 해결되었습니다.
* 글 및 페이지에 저장되지 않은 변경 사항은 자동으로 백업됩니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
13.4:
* Voorbeeldweergave op afstand toegevoegd voor berichten en pagina's.
* Verwijderde berichten blijven in de prullenbak. Ze moeten voor de voorbeeldweergave of het bewerken worden hersteld.
* Opgelost: Klikken op Publiceren bij een privébericht zorgt er nu voor dat het bericht daadwerkelijk privé is, en enkele problemen met linkbewerking zijn opgelost.
* Er worden automatisch back-ups gemaakt van niet-opgeslagen wijzigingen in berichten en pagina's.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
13.4:
* Adicionamos visualização remota a posts e páginas
* Posts enviados para a lixeira continuarão nela. É necessário restaurá-los antes de editar ou visualizar.
* Correções: ao clicar em "Publicar" em um post privado, agora ele é publicado como privado. Também corrigimos alguns problemas com links de edição.
* Agora criamos um backup das alterações não salvas em posts e páginas.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
13.4:
* Поддержка удаленного просмотра для страниц и записей.
* Записи удаленные в корзину должны быть восстановлены из неё перед просмотром или редактированием.
* Исправлена - публикация личной записи будет публиковать запись как личную, также исправлены некоторые проблемы с редактированием ссылок.
* Автоматическое резервное копирование несохраненных изменений в записях и на страницах.

</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
13.4:
* Lagt till stöd för fjärrförhandsvisning av inlägg och sidor.
* Kastade inlägg stannar kvar i papperskorgen. Man måste återställa dem innan man kan redigera eller förhandsvisa dem.
* Rättat: När man klickar på ”Publicera” för ett privat inlägg kommer det verkligen att publiceras privat. Dessutom har några problem med redigering av länkar rättats.
* Osparade ändringar i inlägg och sidor sparas automatiskt i en reservkopia.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
13.4:
* İletiler ve sayfalar için Uzaktan Önizleme desteği eklendi.
* Çöpe atılan iletiler çöpte kalır. Düzenleme veya önizlemeden önce geri getirilmeleri gerekir.
* Düzeltildi: Özel bir iletide “Yayınla” öğesine tıklamak artık iletiyi güvenilir bir biçimde özel olarak yayınlar, bazı bağlantı düzenleme sorunları düzeltildi.
* İleti ve sayfalardaki kaydedilmeyen değişiklikler otomatik olarak yedeklenir.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
13.4：
* 新增了对文章和页面的远程预览支持。
* 已放入回收站的文章依旧在回收站中。这些文章必须先进行还原，才能进行编辑或预览。
* 已修复：现在，在私密文章中点击“发布”按钮，即可放心地将文章发布为私密文章，某些链接编辑问题也得到了解决。
* 系统会自动备份文章和页面中未保存的更改。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
13.4：
* 為文章和頁面新增「遠端預覽」支援。
* 移至垃圾桶的文章會一直留在垃圾桶。若要編輯或預覽，必須先還原這些文章。
* 修正內容：現在按一下私密文章上的「發表」，將能確實以私密狀態發表文章，部分連結編輯問題也已獲得解決。
* 文章和頁面未儲存的變更都會自動備份。
</zh-TW>
