<ar>
15.2:
إضافات محرِّر المكوِّن: تمت إضافة دعم المحرِّر إلى الألوان والتدرجات المحدِّدة للقوالب على مكوِّني الغلاف والزر. تكتمل الآن عمليات رفع مقاطع الفيديو في مكوِّن الغلاف بعد إغلاق المحرِّر. تظهر الآن معلومات قياس عدد المكوِّنات والكلمات والأحرف.

إصلاحات: تم إصلاح مشكلات عرض تفاصيل المقالات في القارئ، ومعالجة اكتمال الرفع في محرِّر المكوِّن، والأعطال التي ستحدث عندما تحوي استجابة واجهة برمجة التطبيقات في ووردبريس نصًا فارغًا.
</ar>
<de-DE>
15,2:
Erweiterungen des Block-Editors: Unterstützt jetzt durch das Theme definierte Farben sowie Verläufe in Cover- und Button-Blöcken. Video-Uploads im Cover-Block werden abgeschlossen, nachdem der Editor geschlossen wurde. Die Kennzahlen für Blöcke, Wörter und Zeichen werden jetzt angezeigt.

Behoben: Probleme mit der Darstellung von Beitragsdetails im Reader, Verarbeitung des Upload-Abschlusses im Block-Editor sowie ein Absturz, wenn die WordPress-API-Reaktion einen leeren Text besitzt.
</de-DE>
<en-US>
15.2:
Block editor additions: Editor support added for theme defined colors and gradients on Cover and Button blocks. Cover block video uploads now completes after the editor has closed. Block, word, and character count metric information are now displayed.

Fixes: Fixed Reader post detail rendering issues, the handling of upload completion in the Block editor, and a crash that would occur when the WordPress API response has an empty body.
</en-US>
<es-ES>
15.2:
Añadidos al editor de bloques: Se ha añadido al editor compatibilidad para colores y degradados definidos por el tema en los bloques de cubierta y botón. El bloque de vídeo de portada se completa ahora después de que el editor se haya cerrado. Ahora se muestra la información métrica del recuento de bloques, palabras y caracteres.

Correcciones: Se han corregido los problemas de procesamiento de detalles de las entradas del lector y el bloqueo en la respuesta de la API de WordPress.
</es-ES>
<fr-CA>
15.2 
Ajouts à l’éditeur de bloc : ajout de la prise en charge de l'éditeur pour les couleurs et les dégradés définis par thème sur les blocs Bannière et Bouton. Le téléchargement des vidéos du bloc Bannière s'achève après la fermeture de l'éditeur. Les informations métriques sur les blocs, les mots et le nombre de caractères sont affichées.

Corrections : Correctifs sur des problèmes de rendu de publication sur le Lecteur et d’un plantage de la réponse de l’API WordPress.
</fr-CA>
<fr-FR>
15.2 
Ajouts à l’éditeur de bloc : ajout de la prise en charge de l'éditeur pour les couleurs et les dégradés définis par thème sur les blocs Bannière et Bouton. Le téléchargement des vidéos du bloc Bannière s'achève après la fermeture de l'éditeur. Les informations métriques sur les blocs, les mots et le nombre de caractères sont affichées.

Corrections : Correctifs sur des problèmes de rendu de publication sur le Lecteur et d’un plantage de la réponse de l’API WordPress.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
15.2:
תוספות לעורך הבלוקים: הוספנו תמיכה בעורך לצבעים ולמעברי צבע שמוגדרים בערכת העיצוב בבלוקים 'כיסוי' ו'כפתור'. ההעלאות של וידאו בבלוק הכיסוי כעת מושלמות לאחר הסגירה של העורך. פרטי הספירה של בלוקים, מילים ותווים מוצגים כעת.

תיקונים: תיקנו בעיות בעיבוד של פרטי הפוסט ב-Reader, את הטיפול בהשלמת ההעלאה בעורך הבלוקים וקריסה שהתרחשה כאשר המענה של API ב-WordPress היה ללא תוכן.
</iw-IL>
<id>
15.2:
Tambahan penyunting blok: Dukungan penyunting ditambahkan untuk warna dan gradasi yang berdasarkan tema pada blok Sampul dan Tombol. Pengunggahan video blok sampul kini selesai setelah penyunting ditutup. Informasi metrik mengenai jumlah blok, kata, dan karakter kini ditampilkan.

Perbaikan: Masalah pemuatan detail pos Pembaca, penanganan penyelesaian unggahan pada penyunting Blok, dan crash yang terjadi ketika respons API WordPress tidak diisi telah diperbaiki.
</id>
<it-IT>
15.2:
Aggiunte all'editor a blocchi: supporto all'editor aggiunto per colori e gradienti specifici del tema sui blocchi Copertina e Pulsante. I caricamenti di video del blocco Copertina vengono completati dopo la chiusura dell'editor. Vengono visualizzate le informazioni di tipo metrico del blocco, del conteggio di parole e caratteri.

Correzioni: corretti problemi di restituzione dei dettagli dell'articolo del Reader e un arresto anomalo in risposta a un API di WordPress.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
15.2 : 
ブロックエディターの追加 : カバーブロックとボタンブロックのテーマ定義カラーとグラデーションにエディターのサポートが追加されました。 エディターを閉じるとカバーブロックの動画アップロードが完了します。 ブロック数、単語数、文字数のメトリック情報が表示されます。

修正 : Reader 投稿の詳細におけるレンダリングの問題、ブロックエディターにおけるアップロード完了処理、および WordPress API の応答に空の本文がある場合にクラッシュする問題を修正しました。
</ja-JP>
<nl-NL>
Blok-editor toevoegingen: Redactionele ondersteuning toegevoegd voor thema gedefinieerde kleuren en kleurverlopen op cover- en knop blokken. Cover blok video-uploads zijn nu voltooid nadat de editor is gesloten. Blok-, woord- en karakter telling metrische informatie wordt nu weergegeven.

Opgelost: Problemen met de weergave van de Reader bericht details, de afhandeling van de upload in de blok-editor, en een crash die zou optreden wanneer de WordPress API-reactie een lege body heeft
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
15.2:
Adições ao editor de blocos: adicionamos suporte aos blocos Cobertura e Botão a cores e gradientes definidos pelo tema . Enviar um vídeo usando o bloco Cobertura agora finaliza o envio mesmo que o editor seja fechado. Exibição de métricas de blocos, palavras e caracteres.

Correções: corrigimos a exibição de detalhes de posts no Leitor, melhoramos como envio de arquivos são tratados no editor de blocos, e corrigimos um conflito com a API do WordPress quando a resposta estiver vazia.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
15.2:
Добавлено в редактор блоков: Поддержка редактором цветов темы и градиентов в блоках кнопки и обложки. Загрузка видео в блок обложки будет завершена даже если редактор будет закрыт. Отображение счетчика блоков, слов и символов.

Исправлено: Отображение подробностей в Чтиве, завершение загрузки в редакторе, падение при пустом ответе WordPress API.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
15.2:
Nytt i blockredigeraren: Stöd i redigeraren för temadefinierade färger och gradienter i omslags- och knappblock. Uppladdning av video för omslagsblock fullföljs även efter redigeraren har stängts. Räknare för block, ord och tecken visas.

Rättelser: Rättat problem i läsaren med att visa inläggsuppgifter och fullföljande av uppladdning i blockredigeraren samt en krasch vid tomt svar från WordPress API.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
15,2:
Blok düzenleyicisi eklemeleri: Kapak ve Düğme bloklarında tema tanımlı renkler ve gradyanlar için düzenleyici desteği eklendi. Kapak bloğu video yüklemeleri, düzenleyici kapatıldıktan sonra tamamlanır. Blok, sözcük ve karakter sayısı ile ilgili ölçüm bilgileri görüntülenir.

Düzeltmeler: Okuyucu gönderim ayrıntısı oluşturma sorunları ve bir WordPress API yanıt kilitlenmesi düzeltildi.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
15.2：
区块编辑器添加内容： 为封面和按钮区块上的主题定义颜色和渐变添加了编辑器支持。 现在，封面区块视频上传在关闭编辑器后完成。 现在显示区块、字词和字符计数指标信息。

修复：修复了阅读器文章详细信息呈现问题、区块编辑器中上传完成的处理以及 WordPress API 响应的正文为空时可能发生的崩溃问题。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
15.2：
區塊編輯器新功能：新增編輯器支援，封面和按鈕區塊可設定佈景主題定義的顏色和漸層色彩。 封面區塊視訊現在會在編輯器關閉後上傳完成。 系統現在會顯示區塊、文字和字元數指標資訊。

修正：修復讀取器文章詳細資料轉譯問題、區塊編輯器中上傳完成的處理工作，以及 WordPress API 回應本文空白時發生的當機情況。
</zh-TW>
