<ar>
18.6:
- يمكنك الآن استخدام وضع علامة على وسم HTML وتغيير نص زر مكوِّن البحث ولون الخلفية.
- ميزات إعداد المحرر الأصلي متاحة للجميع، بما في ذلك شارة المكوِّن الجديد.
- لن تخرج شاشة التعليمات من صندوقها عند تدويرها من الوضع الرأسي إلى الوضع الأفقي.
- أصلحنا مزيدًا من المشكلات الخاصة بالتحميل الموجودة في مكوِّن التضمين.
</ar>
<de-DE>
18.6:
- Du kannst jetzt das Tag „Mark HTML“ nutzen, um den Text und die Hintergrundfarbe des Buttons „Block suchen“.
- Onboarding-Funktionen des nativen Editors, darunter auch das Badge „Neuer Block“, stehen allen zur Verfügung.
- Der Hilfe-Bildschirm bleibt in seinem Rahmen, wenn er von Hoch- zu Querformat gedreht wird.
- Wir haben weitere Ladestörungen des Embed-Blocks behoben.
</de-DE>
<en-US>
18.6:
- You can now use the Mark HTML tag and change the Search block button's text and background color.
- Native editor onboarding features are available to everyone, including the new block badge.
- The Help screen won't break out of its box when rotated between portrait and landscape.
- We fixed more loading glitches in the Embed block.
</en-US>
<es-ES>
18.6:
- Ahora puedes usar la etiqueta HTML Mark y cambiar el texto y el color de fondo del botón del bloque de búsqueda.
- Las características nativas incorporadas del editor están disponibles para todos, incluyendo la nueva insignia de bloque.
- La pantalla de ayuda no se sale de su caja cuando se rota entre retrato y panorámica.
- Hemos corregido más fallos de carga en el bloque de incrustación.
</es-ES>
<fr-CA>
18.6 :
- Vous pouvez désormais utiliser la balise HTML Mark et modifier le texte et la couleur d‘arrière-plan du bouton de bloc Recherche.
- Les fonctionnalités d‘accueil de l‘éditeur natif sont disponibles pour tous, y compris le nouveau badge de bloc.
- L‘écran d‘aide ne sort plus de sa position lorsqu‘il passe du mode Portrait à Paysage.
- Nous avons corrigé d‘autres problèmes de chargement dans le bloc Embarquer.
</fr-CA>
<fr-FR>
18.6 :
- Vous pouvez désormais utiliser la balise HTML Mark et modifier le texte et la couleur d‘arrière-plan du bouton de bloc Recherche.
- Les fonctionnalités d‘accueil de l‘éditeur natif sont disponibles pour tous, y compris le nouveau badge de bloc.
- L‘écran d‘aide ne sort plus de sa position lorsqu‘il passe du mode Portrait à Paysage.
- Nous avons corrigé d‘autres problèmes de chargement dans le bloc Embarquer.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
18.6:
- כעת אפשר להשתמש בתגית 'לסמן HTML' ולשנות את הטקסט וצבע הרקע בכפתור של בלוק החיפוש.
- אפשרויות להתחלת עבודה עם העורך המקורי זמינות לכולם, כולל תג הבלוק החדש.
- המסך 'עזרה' לא יחרוג מהגבולות שלו בעת סיבוב התצוגה מהאורך לרוחב.
- תיקנו בעיות טעינה נוספות בבלוק ההטמעה.
</iw-IL>
<id>
18.6
- You can now use the Mark HTML tag and change the Search block button's text and background colour.
- Native editor onboarding features are available to everyone, including the new block badge.
- The Help screen won't break out of its box when rotated between portrait and landscape.
- We fixed more loading glitches in the Embed block.
</id>
<it-IT>
18.6:
- Ora puoi usare il tag HTML Mark e modificare il testo del pulsante del blocco Cerca e il colore di sfondo.
- Le funzionalità di avviamento dell'editor native sono disponibili per tutti, incluso il nuovo badge del blocco.
- La schermata Guida non si staccherà più dalla sua casella durante la rotazione da orizzontale a verticale e viceversa.
- Abbiamo corretto ulteriori problemi di caricamento nel blocco Incorporamenti.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
18.6:
- Mark HTML タグを使って、「検索」ブロックボタンのテキストや背景色を変更できるようになりました。
- ネイティブエディターのオンボーディング機能は、新しいブロックバッジを含め、だれでも利用できます。
- ヘルプ画面を縦向きや横向きに回転させても、枠からはみ出ないようになりました。
- 埋め込みブロックの読み込みエラーを修正しました。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
18.6:
- 이제는 HTML 표시 태그를 사용하고 검색 블록 버튼의 텍스트와 배경 색상을 변경할 수 있습니다.
- 새 블록 배지를 포함하여 기본적으로 제공되는 편집기 온보딩 기능을 누구나 사용할 수 있습니다.
- 세로와 가로 사이에서 회전할 때 도움말 화면이 상자를 벗어나지 않습니다.
- 임베드 블록의 로딩 결함을 더 해결했습니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
18.6:
- Je kunt nu de HTML mark tag gebruiken, en de tekst en achtergrondkleur van de zoek blok knop wijzigen.
- Native editor onboarding functies zijn voor iedereen beschikbaar, inclusief de nieuwe blok badge.
- Het hulpscherm loopt niet uit zijn box wanneer het wordt gedraaid tussen staand en liggend.
- We hebben meer laadproblemen in het insluit blok opgelost.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
18.6:
- Agora você pode usar a tag HTML Mark para alterar as cores do texto e de fundo do botão do bloco pesquisa.
- Recursos do editor nativo estão disponíveis para todos, incluindo o aviso de novo bloco.
- A tela de ajuda não quebra mais ao trocar entre o modo retrato e paisagem.
- Corrigimos mais erros de carregamento no bloco de mídia incorporada.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
18.6:
- Теперь вы можете использовать HTML-тег mark и изменить цвет текста и фона кнопки блока поиска.
- Стартовые возможности встроенного редактора доступны всем, включая значов нового блока.
- Экран справки не деформируется при повороте между книжной и альбомной ориентацией.
- Мы исправили больше ошибок загрузки в блоке встраивания.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
18.6:
- Nu kan du använda HTML-taggen ”mark” och ändra text- och bakgrundsfärg för sökblockets knapp.
- Välkomstfunktioner för den inbyggda redigeraren är tillgängliga för alla, inklusive det nya block-märket.
- Hjälpsidan hoppar inte längre ut ur sin ruta när man roterar enheten mellan liggande och stående format.
- Vi har rättat några fler laddningsproblem i inbäddningsblocket.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
18.6:
- Artık HTML İşaretleme etiketini kullanabilir ve Arama bloku düğmesinin metin ve arka plan rengini değiştirebilirsiniz.
- Yeni blok rozeti de dahil olmak üzere yerel düzenleyici destek özellikleri artık herkes tarafından kullanılabilir.
- Dikey ve yatay görünüm arasında geçiş yapıldığında Yardım ekranı artık çerçevesinden çıkmıyor.
- Gömülü bloktaki diğer yükleme hatalarını düzelttik.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
18.6：
- 现在，您可以使用 Mark HTML 标签并更改“搜索”区块按钮的文本和背景颜色。
- 已面向所有人开放原生编辑器登录功能，包括新的区块徽章。
-“帮助”屏幕在竖屏和横屏之间旋转时不会再跳出框。
- 我们还修复了嵌更多入区块中的加载故障。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
18.6:
- 你現在可以使用「標記 HTML」標籤並變更搜尋區塊按鈕的文字和背景顏色。
- 人人都能使用原生編輯器入門功能，包括新的區塊徽章。
- 在直向檢視和橫向檢視之間旋轉時，「說明」部分不會超出畫面範圍。
- 我們修正了嵌入內容區塊的其他載入問題。
</zh-TW>
