<ar>
13.9:
• Block editor additions: Added a new Gallery block for creating image galleries using files from your Media Library, along with support for the Preformatted block.
• Block editor enhancements: Added support for settings in the List and Video blocks.
</ar>
<de-DE>
13.9:
• Neu im Block-Editor: Neuer Galerie-Block zur Erstellung von Bildgalerien mit Dateien aus deiner Mediathek sowie Unterstützung des vorformatierten Blocks hinzugefügt.
• Verbesserungen am Block-Editor: Unterstützung für Einstellungen in den Listen- und Video-Blöcken hinzugefügt.
</de-DE>
<en-US>
13.9:
• Block editor additions: Added a new Gallery block for creating image galleries using files from your Media Library, along with support for the Preformatted block.
• Block editor enhancements: Added support for settings in the List and Video blocks.
</en-US>
<es-ES>
13.9:
- Adiciones al editor de bloques: Añadido un nuevo bloque de galería para crear galerías de imágenes usando archivos de tu biblioteca de medios, junto con compatibilidad para el bloque preformateado.
- Mejoras en el editor de bloques: Añadida compatibilidad para los ajustes de los bloques de lista y vídeo.
</es-ES>
<iw-IL>
13.9:
• תוספות לעורך הבלוקים: הוספנו בלוק גלריה חדש ליצירת גלריית תמונות באמצעות קבצים מספריית המדיה שלך ותמיכה בבלוק Preformatted.
• שיפורים בעורך הבלוקים: הוספנו תמיכה להגדרות בבלוק הרשימה ובבלוק הווידאו.
</iw-IL>
<id>
13.9:
• Tambahan pada penyunting blok: Menambahkan blok Galeri yang baru untuk membuat galeri gambar menggunakan file dari Pustaka Media Anda, bersama dengan dukungan untuk blok Yang diformat sebelumnya.
• Peningkatan pada penyunting blok: Menambahkan dukungan untuk pengaturan di blok Daftar dan Video.
</id>
<it-IT>
13.9:
• Aggiunte all'editor dei blocchi: aggiunto un nuovo blocco Galleria per creare gallerie di immagini usando file dalla libreria multimediale, insieme al supporto per il blocco Preformattato.
• Miglioramenti all'editor dei blocchi: aggiunto supporto per le impostazioni nei blocchi Elenco e Video.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
13.9:
•Block editor additions:Added a new Gallery block for creating image galleries using files from your Media Library, along with support for the Preformatted block.
•Block editor enhancements:Added support for settings in the List and Video blocks.
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
13.9:
• 블록 편집기 추가 기능: 미디어 라이브러리의 파일을 사용하여 이미지 갤러리를 만들 수 있는 새로운 갤러리 블록이 사전 서식 지정된 블록 지원과 함께 추가되었습니다.
• 블록 편집기의 향상된 기능: 목록 및 비디오 블록의 설정에 대한 지원이 추가되었습니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
13.9:
• Aanvullingen op de blokeditor: We hebben een nieuw Galerijblok toegevoegd om afbeeldinggalerijen te maken met bestanden uit je Mediabibliotheek, en ondersteuning voor het Vooraf ingesteld-blok.
• Verbeteringen aan de blokeditor: Toegevoegde ondersteuning voor instellingen in de Lijst- en videoblokken.
</nl-NL>
<ru-RU>
13.9:
• Улучшения редактора блоков: добавлен блок галереи для создания галерей из файлов медиатеки, а также поддержка блока преформатированного текста. Возможность настройки блоков списков и видео.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
13.9:
• Nyheter i blockredigeraren: Nytt galleri-block för bildgallerier med filer från mediabiblioteket, och även stöd för ett förformaterat block.
• Förbättringar i blockredigeraren: Nu finns det stöd för inställningar i list- och videoblock.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
13.9:
• Blok düzenleyici eklemeleri: Önceden Biçimli blok desteğinin yanı sıra, Ortam Kütüphanenizdeki dosyaları kullanarak görsel galerileri oluşturmanız için yeni bir Galeri bloku eklendi.
• Blok düzenleyici geliştirmeleri: Liste ve Video bloklarındaki ayarlar için destek eklendi.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
13.9：
•区块编辑器添加内容：添加了一个新的“图库”区块，用于使用媒体库中的文件创建图片库，并支持“预格式化”区块。
•区块编辑器增强功能：添加了对“列表”和“视频”区块中设置的支持。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
13.9：
•區塊編輯器新增功能：已新增「圖庫」區塊，讓你可用媒體庫內的檔案建立圖庫，並取得「未格式化」區塊的支援。
•區塊編輯器增強功能：已新增「清單」和「視訊」區塊內的設定支援。
</zh-TW>
