<en-US>
16.5:
Blocks: We added cross-post support for P2, full-width and wide alignment support in the Columns block, the ability to pick a link in the Image block, and the ability to move a block by long-pressing the up/down buttons. We also addressed an issue in text-based blocks with custom font size.

Activity Log: Track your site activity with filters that sort by date or type.

Site Pages: Copy a page with the Duplicate button.


</en-US>
<ko-KR>
16.5:
블록: P2용 교차 글 지원, 컬럼 블록에서 전체 넓이와 넓은 정렬을 지원, 이미지 블록에서 링크 고르는 기능, 그리고 위/아래 버튼을 길게 눌러 블록이 이동하는 기능을 추가했습니다.

활동 기록: 날짜나 유형으로 정렬하는 필터로 사이트 활동을 추적하세요.

사이트 패이지: 복제 버튼으로 패이지를 복사하세요.


</ko-KR>
<ru-RU>
16.5:
Блоки: Добавлена поддержка кросс-постинга в P2, поддержка полной ширины и широкого выравнивания в блоке столбцов, возможность выбирать ссылку в блоке изображений и возможность перемещать блок, долгим нажатием кнопок вверх / вниз. Исправлена проблема блока текст с пользовательским шрифтом.

Журнал активности: отслеживайте активность на сайте с помощью фильтров, которые сортируются по дате или типу.

Страницы сайта: копируйте страницу с помощью кнопки «Дублировать».
</ru-RU>

<es-ES>
16.5:
Bloques: Hemos añadido compatibilidad para entradas cruzadas para P2, compatibilidad de alineación de ancho completo y amplia en el bloque de columnas, la capacidad de elegir un enlace en el bloque de imagen y la capacidad de mover un bloque manteniendo pulsados los botones arriba/abajo. 

Registro de actividad: Rastrea la actividad de tu sitio con filtros que ordenan por fecha o por tipo.

Páginas del sitio: Copia una página con el botón «Duplicar».
</es-ES>

<sv-SV>
16.5:
Block: Vi har lagt till stöd för korspublicering via P2, stöd för fullbred och bred justering i kolumnblocket, möjlighet att välja länk i bildblocket och att flytta ett block inom en sida med långt tryck på knapparna upp/ned. Dessutom har vi åtgärdat ett problem med anpassad textstorlek i textbaserade block.

Aktivitetslogg: Följ händelserna på din webbplats med filter för sortering på datum eller aktivitetstyp.

Sidor på webbplatsen: Skapa kopia av en sida med dupliceringsknappen.
</sv-SV>

<nl-NL>
16.5:
Blokken: we hebben cross-bericht-ondersteuning toegevoegd voor P2, ondersteuning voor volledige en brede uitlijning in het Kolommen blok, de mogelijkheid om een link te kiezen in het afbeelding-blok en de mogelijkheid om een blok te verplaatsen door lang op de knoppen omhoog/omlaag te drukken. 

Activiteitenlog: houd je site activiteit bij met filters die op datum of type sorteren.

Sitepagina's: kopieer een pagina met de knop Dupliceren.
</nl-NL>

<it-IT>
16.5:
Editor a blocchi: Abbiamo aggiunto il support per il cross-post nei P2, la possibilità di selezionare un link nel blocco immagine, e la possibilità di muovere un blocco premendo a lungo sui bottoni su/giù. 

Activity Log: Ora puoi ordinare l'attività del tuo sito per data e tipo.

Site Pages: Copia una pagina con il bottone Duplica.
</it-IT>
