<en-US>
Dedicated embed blocks for YouTube, Twitter, WordPress, and Vimeo, with URLs that can be edited after they are selected.
The gallery block now adds images even if the post is closed during the upload.
Site comments allow the author’s name, email, and web address to be edited.
You can now contact support directly from the editor screen.
</en-US>
<ar>
18.4: مكوِّنات تضمين مخصصة ليوتيوب، وتويتر، ووردبريس، وفيميو، بالإضافة إلى عناوين URL التي يمكن تحريرها بعد تحديدها. يضيف الآن مكوِّن المعرض صورًا حتى إذا أغلِقت المقالة أثناء الرفع. تسمح تعليقات الموقع بتحرير اسم المؤلف، والبريد الإلكتروني، وعنوان الويب. يمكنك الآن الاتصال بالدعم مباشرة من شاشة المحرِّر.
</ar>
<de-DE>
18.4:
Dedizierte Embed-Blocks für YouTube, Twitter, WordPress und Vimeo mit URLS, die du noch nach dem Aussuchen bearbeiten kannst.
Der Galerieblock fügt jetzt auch Bilder hinzu, wenn der Beitrag während des Hochladens geschlossen wird.
In Website-Kommentaren können der Name des Autors, die E-Mail-Adresse und die Web-Adresse bearbeitet werden.
Du kannst den Support jetzt direkt vom Bildschirm „Editor“ aus kontaktieren.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
18.4:
Los bloques de incrustación específicos para YouTube, Twitter, WordPress y Vimeo cuentan con unas URL que se pueden editar después de que las hayas seleccionado.
Ahora, el bloque de la galería añade imágenes incluso si la entrada se cierra durante la subida.
Los comentarios del sitio permiten editar el nombre, el correo electrónico y la dirección del sitio web del autor.
Ahora, puedes ponerte en contacto con el soporte técnico directamente desde la pantalla del editor.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
18.4 :
Blocs de contenu embarqué dédiés pour YouTube, Twitter, WordPress et Vimeo, avec URL modifiables une fois sélectionnées.
Le bloc Galerie ajoute désormais les images même si l’article de blog est fermé pendant leur chargement.
Les commentaires d’un site permettent de modifier le nom, l’adresse e-mail et l’adresse Web de l’auteur.
Vous pouvez désormais contacter l’assistance directement à partir de l’écran de l’éditeur.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
18.4:
בלוקים ייעודיים להטמעה עבור YouTube, טוויטר, WordPress, ו-Vimeo עם אפשרות לעריכה של כתובת ה-URL גם לאחר שנבחרה.
בלוק הגלריה כעת יכול להוסיף תמונות גם כאשר הפוסט נסגר במהלך ההעלאה.
אפשר לערוך את השם, כתובת האימייל וכתובת האינטרנט של המחבר בתגובות באתר.
כעת אפשר ליצור קשר עם התמיכה ישירות מהמסך של העורך.
</iw-IL>
<id>
18.4:
Blok sematan khusus untuk YouTube, Twitter, WordPress, dan Vimeo, dengan URL yang dapat disunting setelah dipilih.
Blok galeri sekarang dapat menambahkan gambar meski pos terkait telah ditutup saat pengunggahan.
Komentar situs memungkinkan nama, email, dan alamat web penulis disunting.
Sekarang Anda dapat menghubungi dukungan langsung dari layar editor.
</id>
<it-IT>
18.4:
Blocchi incorporati dedicati per YouTube, Twitter, WordPress e Vimeo, con URL che possono essere modificati dopo la loro selezione. 
Il blocco Galleria aggiunge ora immagini perfino se l'articolo viene chiuso durante il caricamento.
I commenti del sito consentono di modificare il nome dell'autore, l'e-mail e l'indirizzo web.
Ora puoi contattare il supporto direttamente dalla schermata dell'editor.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
18.4: 
YouTube、Twitter、WordPress、Vimeo 専用の埋め込みブロックができました。URL は選択後でも編集できます。
ギャラリーブロックではアップロード中に投稿を閉じても画像を追加できるようになりました。
サイトのコメントでは投稿者の名前、メールアドレス、ウェブアドレスを編集できます。
また、エディター画面からサポートに直接問い合わせができるようになりました。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
18.4:
선택한 후 편집할 수 있는 URL이 포함된 유튜브, 트위터, 워드프레스, 비메오 전용 임베드 블록입니다.
이제는 업로드 중 글을 닫아도 갤러리 블록을 통해 이미지가 추가됩니다.
사이트 댓글을 통해 글쓴이 이름, 이메일 및 웹 주소를 편집할 수 있습니다.
이제는 편집기 화면에서 바로 지원팀에 문의할 수 있습니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
18.4:
Insluitblokken speciaal voor YouTube, Twitter, WordPress en Vimeo, met URL's die kunnen worden bewerkt nadat ze zijn geselecteerd.
Met het galerijblok kunnen nu afbeeldingen worden toegevoegd zelfs als het bericht wordt gesloten tijdens het uploaden.
Bij sitereacties kunnen de naam, het e-mailadres en het webadres van de auteur worden bewerkt.
Je kunt nu rechtstreeks contact opnemen met de ondersteuning vanuit het editorscherm.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
18.4:
Blocos de mídia incorporada dedicados para YouTube, Twitter, WordPress e Vimeo, com URLs que podem ser editadas após a seleção.
Agora o bloco de galeria adicionará as imagens mesmo se o post for fechado durante o upload.
Os comentários no site permitem que o endereço da Web, e-mail e nome do autor sejam editados.
Agora você pode falar com o suporte diretamente na tela do editor.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
18.4:
Специальные блоки вставки для YouTube, Twitter, WordPress и Vimeo. Выбрав URL-адрес, его можно изменить.
Теперь блок галереи позволяет добавлять изображения, даже если идёт загрузка, а запись закрыта.
В комментариях к сайту можно изменять имя, электронную почту и веб-адрес автора.
Поддержка доступна прямо на экране редактора.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
18.4:
Dedikerade inbäddningsblock för YouTube, Twitter, WordPress och Vimeo, med URL:er som kan redigeras efter att de har valts.
Galleriblocket lägger nu till bilder även om inlägget är stängt under uppladdningen.
Webbplatskommentarer tillåter att författarens namn, e-postadress och webbadress redigeras.
Du kan nu kontakta supporten direkt från redigerarens skärm.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
18.4:
YouTube, Twitter, WordPress ve Vimeo için, seçildikten sonra düzenlenebilen URL'lere sahip özel gömme blokları.
Galeri bloku, yükleme sırasında gönderi kapatılsa bile artık görsel ekleyebilir.
Site yorumları, yazarın adının, e-postasının ve web adresinin düzenlenmesine izin verir.
Artık doğrudan düzenleyici ekranından desteğe başvurabilirsiniz.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
18.4：
YouTube、Twitter、WordPress 和 Vimeo 的专用嵌入区块，带有可在选中后进行编辑的 URL。
现在，即使在上传过程中关闭文章，画廊区块也会添加图片。
站点评论允许编辑作者的姓名、电子邮件和网址。
现在，您可以直接从编辑器界面联系支持人员。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
18.4：
我們新增了 YouTube、Twitter、WordPress 和 Vimeo 專用嵌入內容區塊，而且現在選取 URL 後仍然可以編輯。
現在即使在圖片上傳過程中關閉文章，仍會在圖庫區塊加入圖片。
現在可以在網站留言中編輯作者的姓名、電子郵件和網址。
你現在可以直接從編輯器畫面聯絡支援團隊。
</zh-TW>
