<en-US>
- Justify buttons properly in the Buttons block.
- See block names in Hebrew and Indonesian.
- See translated featured image and Cover block color settings.
- No longer see the help button in the unsupported block editor.
- Be notified if text/background color combos are hard to read.
- Run into fewer issues when changing the color of non-selected text.
</en-US>
<ar>
19.1:
- اضبط الأزرار بطريقة صحيحة في مكوِّن الأزرار.
- اطلع على أسماء المكوِّن باللغة العبرية والإندونيسية.
- اطلع على إعدادات لون الصورة البارزة المترجمة ومكوِّن الغلاف.
- لم تعد ترى زر المساعدة في محرِّر المكوِّن غير المدعوم.
- يتم إعلامك إذا كان من الصعب قراءة مجموعات ألوان النص/الخلفية.
- واجه مشكلات أقل عند تغيير لون نص غير محدَّد.
</ar>
<de-DE>
19.1:
– Buttons im Button-Block richtig ausrichten.
– Blocknamen auf Hebräisch und Indonesisch anzeigen.
– Übersetzte Farbeinstellungen für Beitragsbild und Cover-Block anzeigen.
– Hilfe-Button im nicht unterstützten Block-Editor nicht mehr sichtbar.
– Benachrichtigung, wenn Kombinationen aus Text-/Hintergrundfarbe schwer lesbar sind.
– Probleme beim Wechseln der Farbe von nicht ausgewähltem Text reduziert.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
19.1:
- Justifica correctamente los botones en el bloque de botón.
- Visualiza los nombres de los bloques en hebreo e indonesio.
- Visualiza la traducción de la imagen destacada y los ajustes de color del bloque de fondo.
- Ya no verás el botón de ayuda en el editor de bloques no compatible.
- Se te notificará si las combinaciones de color entre texto y fondo son difíciles de leer.
- Encontrarás menos problemas al cambiar el color del texto no seleccionado.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
19.1 :
- Justification de boutons correcte dans le bloc de boutons.
- Affichage de noms de blocs en hébreu et indonésien.
- Traduction des réglages de couleurs du bloc d'arrière-plan et de l'image mise en avant.
- Disparition du bouton « aide » dans l’éditeur de blocs non pris en charge.
- Notification en cas de mauvaise lisibilité de la combinaison de couleurs texte/arrière-plan choisie.
- Moins de problèmes lors du changement de couleur d’un texte non sélectionné.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
19.1:
- אפשר ליישר את הכפתור בצורה תקינה בבלוק הכפתורים.
- אפשר להציג את שמות הבלוקים בעברית ובאינדונזית.
- ניתן לראות הגדרות צבע מתורגמות בתמונה המרכזית ובבלוק הכיסוי.
- הסרנו את כפתור העזרה בעורכי בלוקים שאינם נתמכים.
- ניתן לקבל הודעה על שילובים קשים לקריאה בין צבע הטקסט וצבע הרקע.
- יש פחות בעיות כאשר משנים צבע של טקסט שלא נבחר.
</iw-IL>
<id>
19.1:
- Tombol di blok Tombol kini dijajarkan dengan tepat.
- Nama blok kini tersedia dalam bahasa Ibrani dan bahasa Indonesia.
- Terjemahan untuk pengaturan warna blok gambar sorotan dan Sampul kini tersedia.
- Tombol bantuan kini dihapus dari editor blok yang tidak didukung.
- Dapatkan pemberitahuan jika kombinasi warna teks/latar belakang sulit dibaca.
- Sebagian masalah saat mengganti warna dari teks yang tidak dipilih telah teratasi.
</id>
<it-IT>
19.1:
- Giustifica i pulsanti in modo corretto nel blocco Pulsanti.
- Visualizza i nomi dei blocchi in ebraico e indonesiano.
- Visualizza le impostazioni delle immagini in evidenza e dei colori del blocco Copertina tradotte.
- Non è più visibile il pulsante di supporto nell'editor a blocchi non supportato.
- Ricevi una notifica se le combinazioni di colori del testo/di sfondo non sono adatte alla lettura.
- Incorri in meno problemi con la modifica del colore del testo non selezionato.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
19.1:
- 「ボタン」ブロックのボタン配置の改善。
- ヘブライ語とインドネシア語でのブロック名の表示。
- 翻訳されたアイキャッチ画像と「カバー」ブロックの色設定の表示。
- サポートされていないブロックエディターでのヘルプボタンの非表示。
- テキストと背景色の組み合わせによって読みづらさが生じる場合の通知。
- 選択されていないテキストの色を変更する際に生じる問題の削減。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
19.1:
- 버튼 블록에서 버튼 양쪽이 적절히 맞춰집니다.
- 히브리어와 인도네시아어로 블록 이름이 표시됩니다.
- 번역된 특성 이미지 및 커버 블록 색상 설정이 표시됩니다.
- 지원되지 않는 블록 편집기에 더는 도움말 버튼이 표시되지 않습니다.
- 텍스트/배경 색상 조합이 판독하기 어려우면 알림이 표시됩니다.
- 선택하지 않은 텍스트 색상을 변경할 때 문제가 적게 발생합니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
19.1:
- Knoppen worden correct uitgelijnd in het knopblok.
- Namen van blokken zijn nu beschikbaar in het Hebreeuws en Indonesisch.
- De kleurinstellingen van uitgelichte afbeeldingen en omslagafbeeldingblokken zijn vertaald.
- De help-knop is niet meer zichtbaar in de niet-ondersteunde blokeditor.
- Krijg een melding als de combinatie van de achtergrondkleur en de tekstkleur lastig te lezen is.
- Er zijn minder problemen bij het veranderen van de tekstkleur van niet-geselecteerde tekst.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
19.1:
- Justifique os botões de forma adequada no bloco de botões.
- Veja os nomes de blocos em hebraico e indonésio.
- Veja a tradução das configurações de cor do bloco de cobertura e imagem destacada.
- Diga adeus ao botão de ajuda no editor de blocos incompatíveis.
- Receba uma notificação se as combinações de cor de fundo e de texto dificultarem a leitura.
- Tenha menos problemas na alteração da cor do texto não selecionado.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
19.1:
— Возможность корректного выравнивания кнопок в блоке кнопок.
— Просмотр имён блоков на иврите и индонезийском языке.
— Наличие перевода для избранного изображения и настроек цвета блока обложки.
— Исчезновение кнопки справки в неподдерживаемом редакторе блоков.
— Уведомления при неудачных сочетаниях цвета текста и фона, которые делают текст трудночитаемым.
— Уменьшение числа проблем, приводящих к изменению цвета невыбранного текста.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
19.1:
- Justera knappar korrekt i blocket Knappar.
- Se blocknamn på hebreiska och indonesiska.
- Se översättning av utvald bild och färginställningarna för blocket Omslag.
- Hjälpknappen visas inte längre i blockredigeraren som inte stöds.
- Få notiser om kombinationer av text-/bakgrundsfärger gör det svårt att läsa texten.
- Färre problem med att ändra färg på ej markerad text.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
19.1:
- Düğmeler blokundaki düğmeleri düzgün şekilde hizalayın.
- İbranice ve Endonezyaca blok adlarına bakın.
- Çevrilmiş öne çıkan görsel ve Kapak bloku renk ayarlarını görün.
- Desteklenmeyen blok düzenleyicide artık yardım düğmesini göremezsiniz.
- Metin/arka plan rengi kombinasyonlarının okunması zor olduğunda bildirim alın.
- Seçilmeyen metnin rengini değiştirirken daha az sorunla karşılaşın.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
19.1:
- 在按钮区块里正确的对齐按钮。
- 看区块的名字的希伯来和印度尼西亚的语言翻译。
- 看特色图片区块和封面区块的设置的语言翻译。
- 不再看到帮助按钮在不支持的区块编辑器。
- 接收通告当文本和背景的颜色组合难以阅读。
- 遇到比较少问题当要更改未选择的文本的颜色。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
19.1:
- 在按鈕區塊裏正確的對齊按鈕。
- 看區塊的名字的希伯來和印度尼西亞的語言翻譯。
- 看特色圖片區塊和封面區塊的設置的語言翻譯。
- 不再看到幫助按鈕在不支持的區塊編輯器。
- 接收通告當文本和背景的顔色組合難以閱讀。
- 遇到比較少問題當要更改未選擇的文本的顔色。
</zh-TW>
