<en-US>
- Sign up through WordPress.com and create sites in Jetpack
- Use the Reader in Jetpack
- See notifications in new comment editor
- Get a fix for the flickering Page/Site preview
- Keep editor story blocks from closing when memory is low
</en-US>
<ar>
19.3:
- التسجيل من خلال ووردبريس.كوم وإنشاء مواقع في Jetpack
- استخدام القارئ في Jetpack
- الاطلاع على التنبيهات في محرِّر التعليقات الجديد
- الحصول على إصلاح لصفحة الوميض/معاينة الموقع
- منع مكوِّنات قصة المحرِّر من الإغلاق عندما تكون الذاكرة منخفضة
</ar>
<de-DE>
19.3:
– Auf WordPress.com registrieren und Websites in Jetpack erstellen
– Den Reader in Jetpack nutzen
– Benachrichtigungen im neuen Kommentar-Editor anzeigen
– Fehlerkorrektur für das Flimmern der Seiten-/Websitevorschau
– Story-Blocks im Editor werden bei geringem Speicherplatz nicht mehr geschlossen
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
19.3:
- Regístrate a través de WordPress.com y crea sitios en Jetpack.
- Utiliza el Lector en Jetpack.
- Consulta las notificaciones en el nuevo editor de comentarios.
- Consigue una corrección para el parpadeo de la vista previa de página o sitio.
- Evita que se cierren los bloques de historias del editor cuando haya poca memoria.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
19,3 :
- Inscrivez-vous WordPress.com et créez des sites dans Jetpack
- Utilisez le lecteur dans Jetpack
- Les notifications s’affichent dans le nouvel éditeur de commentaires
- Correction du vacillement de l’aperçu des pages/du site
- L’éditeur du bloc Story ne peut plus se fermer lorsque la mémoire est faible
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
19.3:
- להירשם דרך WordPress.com וליצור אתרים ב-Jetpack
- להשתמש ב-Reader ב-Jetpack
- להציג הודעות בעורך התגובות
- לתקן את התצוגה המקדימה המהבהבת של עמודים/אתרים
- למנוע סגירת בלוקים של סטורי של עורכים כשאין הרבה מקום בזיכרון
</iw-IL>
<id>
19.3:
- Daftar melalui WordPress.com dan buat situs di Jetpack
- Gunakan Pembaca di Jetpack
- Lihat pemberitahuan di editor komentar baru
- Perbaiki efek pratinjau Halaman/Situs yang mengganggu
- Jaga blok cerita editor tetap terbuka saat memori rendah
</id>
<it-IT>
19.3:
- Iscriviti tramite WordPress.com e crea siti in Jetpack
- Usa il Reader in Jetpack
- Visualizza le notifiche nel nuovo editor dei commenti
- Ottieni una correzione allo sfarfallio dell'anteprima di Pagina/Sito
- Impedisci la chiusura dei blocchi Storia dell'editor quando la memoria non è sufficiente
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
19.3:
- WordPress.com から登録して Jetpack でサイトを作成
- Jetpack で Reader を使用
- 新しいコメントエディターで通知を確認
- ページまたはサイトのプレビューでのちらつきを修正
- メモリ不足でエディターのストーリーブロックが閉じる問題を修正
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
19.3:
- 워드프레스닷컴을 통해 가입하고 젯팩에서 사이트 생성
- 젯팩에서 리더 사용
- 새 댓글 편집기에 알림 표시
- 페이지/사이트 미리보기 명멸 문제 해결
- 메모리 부족 시 편집기 스토리 블록 종료 방지
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
19.3:
- Meld je aan via WordPress.com en maak in Jetpack een site aan
- Gebruik de Reader in Jetpack
- Zie meldingen in de nieuwe opmerkingseditor
- Los het knipperen van de voorbeeldweergave van een pagina of site op
- Stop het sluiten van verhaalblokken in de editor bij een laag geheugen
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
19.3:
- Inscreva-se no WordPress.com e crie sites no Jetpack
- Use o leitor no Jetpack
- Veja as notificações no novo editor de comentários
- Corrija a oscilação na visualização da página/site
- Evite que os blocos de story do editor fechem quando há pouca memória
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
19.3:
— Регистрация через WordPress.com и создание сайтов в приложении Jetpack
— Использование Обозревателя в приложении Jetpack
— Просмотр уведомлений в новом редакторе комментариев
— Исправленный эффект мерцания на странице предварительного просмотра
— Блоки с историей редактора не закрываются при недостаточном объеме памяти
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
19.3:
- Registrera dig via WordPress.com och skapa webbplatser med Jetpack
- Använd läsaren i Jetpack
- Se notiser i den nya kommentarsredigeraren
- Få en korrigering av den flimrande sid-/webbplatsförhandsgranskningen
- Se till att redigerarens berättelseblock inte stängs vid lågt minne
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
19.3:
- - WordPress.com üzerinden kaydolun ve Jetpack'te siteler oluşturun
- Jetpack'te Okuyucuyu kullanın
- Yeni yorum düzenleyicide bildirimleri görün
- Titreyen Sayfa/Site önizlemesi için bir düzeltme alın
- Bellek azaldığında düzenleyici hikaye bloklarının kapanmasını önleyin
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
19.3：
- 通过 WordPress.com 注册并在 Jetpack 中创建站点
- 在 Jetpack 中使用阅读器
- 在新的评论编辑器中查看通知
- 修复了页面/站点预览闪烁的问题
- 防止内存不足时编辑器故事区块关闭
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
19.3：
- 透過 WordPress.com 登入並在 Jetpack 中建立網站
- 在 Jetpack 中使用閱讀器
- 在新的留言編輯器中查看通知
- 修正頁面/網站預覽的閃爍問題
- 防止編輯器動態區塊在記憶體不足時關閉
</zh-TW>
