<en-US>
Lots of improvements in the block editor! We fixed an image displaying issue, a toolbar issue affecting devices set to an RTL language, and made many updates to the Embed block, including enabling WordPress, Instagram, and Vimeo previews and offering options to retry or convert media into a link if it’s not embeddable.

Other updates include a fix affecting .mp4 video on some sites, and streamlining My Site menu labels (“Posts” and “Pages”).
</en-US>
<ar>
18.3:
الكثير من التحسينات في محرِّر المكوِّن! قمنا بإصلاح مشكلة شريط الأدوات التي تؤثر في الأجهزة التي تم تعيينها إلى لغة RTL، وأجرينا العديد من التحديثات على مكوِّن التضمين، بما في ذلك تمكين معاينات ووردبريس وإنستغرام وفيميو وتقديم خيارات لإعادة تجربة الوسائط أو تحويلها إلى رابط إذا لم تكن قابلة للتضمين.

تتضمن بعض التحديثات الأخرى إصلاحًا يؤثر في مقاطع الفيديو التي تكون بتنسيق .mp4 على بعض المواقع وتبسيط تسميات قوائم موقعي ("المقالات" و"الصفحات").
</ar>
<de-DE>
18.3:
Wir haben Probleme im Block-Editor mit der Werkzeugleiste bei Geräten mit linksläufiger Sprache behoben und einige Updates am Embed-Block vorgenommen, u. a. eine Vorschau für WordPress, Instagram und Vimeo sowie Optionen zum Wiederholen oder Konvertieren von Medien in einen Link.

Wir haben außerdem einen Fehler behoben, der auf manchen Websites bei Videos auftrat, und die „Meine Website“-Menübeschriftungen aktualisiert („Beiträge“ und „Seiten“).
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
18.3:
En el editor de bloques, hemos solucionado un problema con la barra de herramientas en los dispositivos configurados en un idioma RTL. Además, hemos realizado actualizaciones en el bloque de incrustar, como activar las vistas previas de WordPress, Instagram y Vimeo y añadir opciones para reintentar o convertir los medios en un enlace.

También se incluye una corrección que afecta a los videos en algunos sitios y se han actualizado las etiquetas del menú de Mi Sitio ("Entradas" y "Páginas").
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
18.3 :
Dans l’éditeur de blocs, nous avons résolu un problème de barre d’outils sur les appareils utilisant une langue RTL et avons mis à jour les blocs de contenu embarqué, permettant notamment les aperçus WordPress, Instagram et Vimeo, et offrant l’option de réessayer ou de convertir le média.

Nous avons également corrigé un problème affectant les vidéos sur certains sites, et simplifié les libellés du menu Mon site (« Articles » et « Pages »).
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
18.3:
המון שיפורים בעורך הבלוקים! תיקנו בעיה בסרגל הכלים שהשפיעה על מכשירים שמוגדרים לשפה שנקראת מימין לשמאל והוספנו הרבה עדכונים לבלוק ההטמעה, כולל הפעלה של תצוגות מקדימות של תוכן מ-WordPress, מאינסטגרם ומ-Vimeo ואפשרויות לנסות שוב או להמיר את המדיה לקישורים אם סוג המדיה לא ניתן להטמעה.

עדכונים אחרים כוללים תיקון שהשפיע על סרטוני וידאו בפורמט ‎.mp4 בחלק מהאתרים ושיפור בתצוגה של תוויות התפריט 'האתר שלי' ('פוסטים' ו'עמודים').
</iw-IL>
<id>
18.3:
Di Editor blok, kami memperbaiki masalah bilah peralatan pada perangkat yang disetel ke bahasa RTL, dan membuat pembaruan pada blok Sematan, seperti mengaktifkan pratinjau WordPress, Instagram, dan Vimeo dan menambahkan pilihan untuk mencoba lagi atau mengonversi media menjadi tautan.

Pembaruan lainnya mencakup perbaikan yang memengaruhi video .mp4 di beberapa situs, dan memperbarui label menu Situs Saya (“Pos” dan “Halaman”).
</id>
<it-IT>
18.3:
Nell'editor a blocchi, risolto un problema alla barra degli strumenti per i dispositivi impostati su una lingua RTL ed eseguito aggiornamenti al blocco Incorporamenti, come l'abilitazione delle anteprime di WordPress, Instagram e Vimeo e l'aggiunta di opzioni per riprovare o convertire gli elementi multimediali in un link.

Ulteriori aggiornamenti: una correzione che interessava i video su alcuni siti e 'aggiornamento delle etichette del menu Il mio sito ("Articoli" e "Pagine").
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
18.3:
ブロックエディターが多くの点で改良されました。 右から左に表示される言語に設定されているデバイスに影響を及ぼすツールバーの問題を修正しました。また、WordPress、Instagram、Vimeo でのプレビューの有効化や、メディアを埋め込めない場合に埋め込みをリトライしたり、リンクに変換したりするためのオプションの導入など、埋め込みブロックに対して多数アップデートを行っています。

一部のサイトの .mp4 動画に影響する問題の修正や、「参加サイト」メニューのラベルの整理 (「投稿」と「ページ」) なども行っています。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
18.3:
블록 편집기가 아주 많이 개선되었습니다! RTL 언어로 설정된 기기에 영향을 주는 도구 모음 문제를 해결했으며, WordPress, Instagram, Vimeo 미리보기를 활성화하고 미디어를 임베드할 수 없는 경우 다시 시도하거나 링크로 변환하는 옵션을 제공하는 등 임베드 블록을 많이 업데이트했습니다.

기타 업데이트에는 일부 사이트의 .mp4 비디오에 영향을 주는 수정 사항과 "글"과 "페이지"로 간소화한 내 사이트 메뉴 레이블이 포함됩니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
18.3:
We hebben in blokeditor een probleem met de werkbalk opgelost dat apparaten beïnvloedde die waren ingesteld op een RTL-taal. We hebben ook veel updates doorgevoerd voor het insluitblok, waaronder voorbeeldweergaven inschakelen van WordPress, Instagram en Vimeo en de mogelijkheid toegevoegd om opnieuw te proberen of media te converteren naar een link.

Andere updates omvatten een oplossing voor problemen met video’s op een aantal sites en nieuwe menulabels van Mijn site (‘Berichten’ en ‘Pagina’s’).
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
18.3:
No editor de blocos, corrigimos um erro na barra de ferramentas de dispositivos configurados em RTL e fizemos atualizações no bloco de mídia incorporada, como habilitar prévias para o WordPress, Instagram e Vimeo e incluir a opção de tentar novamente ou converter a mídia em um link.

Além disso, corrigimos um bug que afetava vídeos em alguns sites e atualizamos os rótulos do menu Meu site (agora "Posts" e "Páginas").
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
18.3:
В редакторе блоков исправлена проблема с панелью инструментов на устройствах, где выбран язык с написанием справа налево. Обновлены некоторые функции в блоке "Вставка", добавлены предварительный просмотр элементов WordPress, Instagram и Vimeo и возможности повторной вставки и преобразования медиафайла в ссылку.

Кроме того, устранена ошибка с воспроизведением видеофайлов на некоторых сайтах, улучшены ярлыки меню "Мой сайт" ("Записи" и "Страницы").
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
18.3:
I blockredigeraren har vi åtgärdat ett verktygsfältsproblem på enheter inställda på ett RTL-språk och genomfört uppdateringar av inbäddningsblocket. Bland annat har vi aktiverat WordPress-, Instagram- och Vimeo-förhandsgranskningar och lagt till alternativ för att försöka igen eller konvertera mediainnehållet till en länk.

Ytterligare uppdateringar inkluderar en korrigering som påverkar videofiler på vissa webbplatser och en uppdatering av etiketterna i menyn Min webbplats ("Inlägg" och "Sidor").
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
18.3:
Blok düzenleyicide, RTL diline ayarlanmış cihazlarda araç çubuğunda yaşanan bir sorunu düzelttik ve Gömülü blokta WordPress, Instagram ve Vimeo önizlemelerini etkinleştirmek, medyayı yeniden denemek veya bir bağlantıya dönüştürmek için seçenekler eklemek gibi güncellemeler yaptık.

Diğer güncellemeler olarak, bazı sitelerdeki videoyu etkileyen bir düzeltmeyi ve Sitem menü etiketlerinin (“Gönderiler” ve “Sayfalar”) güncellenmesini sayabiliriz.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
18.3：
区块编辑器中有许多改进！ 我们修复了影响将设备设置为 RTL 语言的工具栏问题，并对嵌入区块进行了许多更新，包括启用 WordPress、Instagram 和 Vimeo 预览，并在无法嵌入媒体时提供了重试媒体嵌入或将媒体转换为链接的选项。

其他更新包括修复了影响某些站点上 .mp4 视频的问题，以及简化了“我的站点”菜单标签（“文章”和“页面”）。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
18.3:
我們改善了區塊編輯器的諸多功能！ 修正了讓裝置無法選擇 RTL 語言的工具列問題，也對嵌入內容區塊做了諸多更新，包括啟用 WordPress、Instagram 和 Vimeo 預覽，並提供了重試或將媒體轉換成連結的選項 (如果媒體不能嵌入的話)。

其他更新包括修正了某些網站 .mp4 影片的問題，以及簡化了「我的網站」選單標籤 (現在是「文章」和「頁面」)。
</zh-TW>
