<en-US>
Embedding external content just got easier with the new Facebook, Instagram, Loom, and Smartframe embed blocks.

Plus, we now detect embeddable URLs when pasted into an empty paragraph, and we fixed a bug with prevented embedded URLs from being edited.

Finally, Pullquote and Preformatted blocks now have customizable text and background color.
</en-US>
<ar>
18.5:
أصبح تضمين المحتوى الخارجي أكثر سهولة باستخدام مكوِّنات تضمين فيسبوك وإنستغرام وLoom وSmartframe الجديدة.

كن على اطلاع دائمًا بشأن المحادثات التي تقوم بمتابعتها من خلال التنبيهات المنبثقة للقارئ الجديد الخاصة بمحادثات تعليقات المقالة التي تتم متابعتها.

بالإضافة إلى ذلك، يمكنك الآن تخصيص لون النص والخلفية في المكوِّنات المهيأة والمنسَّقة سابقًا.
</ar>
<de-DE>
18.5:
Das Einbetten externer Inhalte ist jetzt noch einfacher: mit den neuen Embed-Blöcken für Facebook, Instagram, Loom und Smartframe.

Außerdem erkennen wir jetzt einbettbare URLs, wenn sie in einen leeren Absatz eingefügt werden, und wir haben einen Fehler behoben, durch den eingebettete URLs nicht bearbeitet werden konnten.

Und bei Pullquote- sowie Vorformatiert-Blöcken können jetzt Text und Hintergrundfarbe angepasst werden.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
18.5:
La incrustación de contenido externo resulta más fácil con los nuevos bloques de incrustar para Facebook, Instagram, Loom y Smartframe.

Además, ahora detectamos las URL que se puedan incrustar al pegarlas en un párrafo vacío. También hemos solucionado un error por el que no se podían editar las URL incrustadas.

Para terminar, ahora se puede personalizar el texto y el color de fondo de los bloques Preformateados y Párrafo de cita.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
18.5 :
L’intégration de contenu externe est devenue plus facile grâce aux nouveaux blocs de contenu embarqué Facebook, Instagram, Loom et Smartframe.

De plus, nous détectons désormais les URL intégrables lorsqu’elles sont collées dans un paragraphe vide, et nous avons résolu un bogue qui empêchait la modification des URL intégrées.

Enfin, les blocs de citation en exergue et préformatés ont désormais un texte et une couleur d’arrière-plan personnalisables.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
18.5:
ההטמעה של תוכן קלה עכשיו יותר עם בלוקים להטמעת תוכן של פייסבוק, אינסטגרם, Loom ו-Smartframe.

בנוסף, אנחנו כעת מזהים כתובות URL כאשר הן מודבקות בפסקה ריקה ותיקנו באג שמנע עריכה של כתובות URL מוטמעות.

אחרון חביב, בלוקים של ציטוטים ו-Preformatted כוללים אפשרות התאמה לטקסט ולצבע הרקע.
</iw-IL>
<id>
18.5:
Menyematkan konten eksternal jadi lebih mudah dengan blok sematan Facebook, Instagram, Loom, dan Smartframe yang baru.

Sekarang kami juga mendeteksi URL yang dapat disematkan saat ditempelkan ke paragraf kosong, serta memperbaiki bug yang mencegah URL sematan untuk disunting.

Terakhir, sekarang teks dan warna latar belakang untuk blok Kutipan Besar dan blok Praformat dapat disesuaikan.
</id>
<it-IT>
18.5:
Incorporare contenuti esterni è diventato più semplice con i nuovi blocchi Incorporamenti Facebook, Instagram, Loom e Smartframe.

Inoltre, ora rileviamo gli URL incorporabili quando vengono incollati in un paragrafo vuoto e abbiamo corretto un bug che impediva la modifica degli URL incorporati.

Infine, i blocchi Citazione evidenziata e Preformattato hanno ora testo e colore di sfondo personalizzabili.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
18.5:
Facebook、Instagram、Loom、SmartFrame の埋め込みブロックで、外部コンテンツの埋め込みが簡単になりました。

さらに、空の段落にペーストする際に埋め込み可能な URL を検出できるようになり、埋め込み URL を編集できないバグが修正されました。

最後に、プルクオートブロックと整形済みブロックで、テキスト色と背景色をカスタマイズできるようになりました。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
18.5:
새로운 페이스북, 인스타그램, Loom 및 Smartframe 임베드 블록 덕분에 외부 콘텐츠를 임베드하는 작업이 더 쉬워졌습니다.

또한, 이제는 빈 문단에 붙여넣을 때 임베드 가능한 URL이 감지되며, 임베드된 URL을 편집할 수 없었던 버그는 수정했습니다.

마지막으로, 이제는 요약글 블록과 정형화된 형식 블록에 사용자 정의 가능한 텍스트와 배경 색상이 있습니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
18.5:
Het insluiten van externe content is nu eenvoudiger met de nieuwe insluitblokken voor Facebook, Instagram, Loom en Smartframe.

Daarbij detecteren we insluitbare URL's wanneer deze worden geplakt in een lege paragraaf en hebben we een probleem met het bewerken van ingesloten URL's opgelost.

Ten slotte zijn Pullquote- en vooraf ingestelde blokken nu voorzien van aanpasbare tekst en een achtergrondkleur.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
18.5:
Incorporar conteúdo externo ficou ainda mais fácil com os novos blocos de mídia incorporada para Facebook, Instagram, Loom e SmartFrame.

Além disso, corrigimos um bug que impedia a edição de URLs incorporáveis e agora as detectamos quando coladas em um parágrafo vazio.

Por fim, os blocos de citação destacada e pré-formatado agora têm texto personalizado e cor de fundo.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
18.5:
Встраивание внешнего содержимого стало еще проще с новыми блоками встраивания Facebook, Instagram, Loom и Smartframe.

Всегда будьте в курсе бесед (и комментариев), на которые вы подписаны, с помощью новых push-уведомлений в Чтиве.

Кроме того, теперь вы можете настроить цвет текста и фона в блоках выдержки и преформатированного текста.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
18.5:
De nya inbäddningsblocken för Facebook, Instagram, Loom och Smartframe gör att det är enklare än någonsin att bädda in externt innehåll.

Vi kan nu även detektera inbäddningsbara URL:er som klistras in i ett tomt stycke och vi har åtgärdat ett fel som gjorde att det inte gick att redigera inbäddade URL:er.

Slutligen har markerat citat-block och förformaterade block nu anpassningsbar text och bakgrundsfärg.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
18.5:
Yeni Facebook, Instagram, Loom ve Smartframe gömülü bloklarıyla harici içeriği gömmek artık daha kolay.

Ayrıca artık boş bir paragrafa yapıştırıldığında gömülebilir URL'ler algılanabiliyor ve gömülü URL'lerin düzenlenmesini engelleyen bir hata düzeltildi.

Son olarak, Alıntı ve Önceden Biçimlendirilmiş blokları artık özelleştirilebilir metin ve arka plan rengine sahip.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
18.5：
新的 Facebook、Instagram、Loom 和 Smartframe 嵌入区块让嵌入外部内容变得更加容易。

此外，我们现在还可以在粘贴到空段落时检测可嵌入 URL，并修复了阻止对嵌入的 URL 进行编辑的错误。

最后，醒目引文和预格式化区块中现在可以自定义文本和背景颜色。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
18.5：
全新的 Facebook、Instagram、Loom 和 Smartframe 嵌入區塊，讓嵌入外部內容變得更簡單。

另外，我們現在能偵測到貼至空白段落的可嵌入 URL，並修正了無法編輯嵌入 URL 的錯誤。

最後，現在可於重要引述和預設格式區塊自訂文字和背景色彩。
</zh-TW>
