<en-US>
- Highlight text with any color in Paragraph blocks.
- Create new Gallery blocks with the new design and auto-convert old galleries to match.
- Undo and redo changes when formatting link text in blocks.
- Load faster when reblogging posts and sharing text from other apps.
- See background colors in pre-formatted blocks on sites with standard themes.
</en-US>
<ar>
18.9:
- قم بتمييز النص باستخدام أي لون في مكوِّنات الفقرة.
- قم بإنشاء مكوِّنات معرض جديدة باستخدام التصميم الجديد وقم بتحويل المعارض القديمة تلقائيًا للمطابقة.
- تراجع عن التغييرات وقم بإعادتها عند تنسيق نص الرابط في المكوِّنات.
- قم بالتحميل بشكل أسرع عند إعادة تدوين المقالات ومشاركة نص من تطبيقات أخرى.
</ar>
<de-DE>
18.9:
- Hebe Text in Absätzen mit beliebigen Farben hervor.
- Erstelle neue Galerieblöcke mit neuem Design und konvertiere alte Galerien automatisch, damit sie dazu passen.
- Mache Änderungen beim Formatieren von Linktext in Blöcken rückgängig oder stelle sie wieder her.
- Schnelleres Laden beim Rebloggen von Beiträgen und beim Teilen von Text aus anderen Apps.
- Hintergrundfarben in vorformatierten Blöcken funktionieren nun auf Websites mit Standardthemen.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
18.9:
- Resaltar el texto con cualquier color en los bloques de párrafo.
- Crear nuevos bloques de Galería con el nuevo diseño y convertir automáticamente las galerías antiguas para que coincidan.
- Deshacer y rehacer los cambios al formato del texto de los enlaces en los bloques.
- Carga más rápida al volver a bloguear entradas y compartir texto desde otras aplicaciones.
- Ver colores de fondo en bloques pre formateados en sitios con temas standard.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
18.9 :
- Surlignez du texte dans n’importe quelle couleur dans les blocs Paragraphe.
- Créez de blocs Galerie avec le nouveau design et convertissez automatiquement vos anciennes galeries.
- Annulez et rétablissez des modifications lors du formatage de liens dans les blocs.
- Chargement plus rapide lors du reblogging d’articles et du partage de texte depuis d’autres applications.
 - Les blocks pré-formattés affichent les couleurs de fond sur les sites utiilisant des themes standards.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
18.9:
- אפשר להגדיש טקסט בכל צבע שרוצים בבלוקים של פסקה רגילה.
- אפשר ליצור בלוקים חדשים של גלריה עם העיצוב החדש ולהמיר באופן אוטומטי גלריות ישנות כדי להתאים אותן.
- אפשר לבטל שינויים או לבצע אותם שוב כאשר מעצבים טקסט של קישור בבלוקים.
- טעינה מהירה יותר בפרסום מחדש של פוסטים בבלוג ובשיתוף של טקסט מאפליקציות אחרות.
- אפשר לראות צבעי רקע של בלוקים מעוצבים מראש באתרים עם ערכות עיצוב סטנדרטיות.
</iw-IL>
<id>
18.9:
- Sorot teks dengan warna apa pun di blok Paragraf.
- Buat blok Galeri baru dengan desain baru untuk mengonversikan galeri lama secara otomatis agar sesuai.
- Urungkan dan ulangi perubahan saat memformat teks tautan di blok.
- Muat lebih cepat saat melakukan reblog pos dan membagikan teks dari aplikasi lain.
</id>
<it-IT>
18.9:
- Evidenzia il testo con qualsiasi colore nei blocchi Paragrafo.
- Crea nuovi blocchi Galleria con il nuovo design e converti automaticamente le vecchie gallerie affinché corrispondano.
- Annulla e ripeti le modifiche quando formatti il testo dei link nei blocchi.
- Carica più rapidamente quando ripubblichi articoli e condividi testo da altre app.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
18.9:
- 段落ブロックで任意の色を使ってテキストを強調表示できます。
- 新しいデザインのギャラリーブロックを作成したり、それに合わせて古いギャラリーを自動変換したりできます。
- ブロック内のリンクテキストの書式を設定する際に、変更を元に戻したり、やり直したりできます。
- 投稿をリブログしたり、他のアプリからテキストを共有したりする際の読み込みが速くなりました。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
18.9:
- 원하는 색상으로 문단 블록의 텍스트를 강조합니다.
- 새 디자인으로 새 갤러리 블록을 생성하고 기존 갤러리가 일치하도록 자동 변환합니다.
- 블록의 링크 텍스트 형식 지정 시 변경사항 실행 취소/재실행이 가능합니다.
- 글을 블로그에 다시 올리고 다른 앱의 텍스트를 공유할 때 더 빨리 로드합니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
18.9:
- Markeer tekst in iedere kleur in paragraafblokken.
- Creëer nieuwe galerijblokken met het nieuwe ontwerp, en pas oude galerijen aan zodat ze matchen.
- Maak veranderingen ongedaan of juist opnieuw tijdens het formatteren van linktekst in blokken.
- Snellere laadtijden tijdens het rebloggen van berichten en het delen van tekst uit andere apps.
- Zie de achtergrondkleur in gepreformatteerde blokken op sites met standaardthema’s.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
18.9:
- Destaque o texto com qualquer cor nos blocos de parágrafo.
- Crie novos blocos de galeria com o novo design e converta automaticamente galerias antigas para que combinem.
- Desfaça e refaça as alterações ao formatar o texto do link em blocos.
- Carregue mais rápido ao bloquear posts e compartilhar texto de outros aplicativos.
- Veja cores de fundo em blocos pré-formatados em sites com temas padrão.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
18.9:
- Выделяйте текст любым цветом в блоках абзаца.
- Создавайте новые блоки галереи с новым дизайном и автоматически конвертируйте старые галереи.
- Отмена и повтор изменений при форматировании текста ссылки в блоках.
- Быстрая загрузка при перепубликации записец и обмене текстом из других приложений.
- Просматривайте цвета фона в пре-форматированных блоках на сайтах со стандартными темами. 
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
18.9:
– Framhäv text med valfri färg i styckblock.
– Skapa nya gallierblock i det nya utförandet och konvertera automatiskt äldre gallerier så att de blir likadana.
– Ångra och gör om ändringar i formateringen av länkad text i block.
– Snabbare sidladdning när du rebloggar inlägg eller delar text från andra appar.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
18.9:
- Paragraf bloklarında metni herhangi bir renkle vurgulayın.
- Yeni tasarımla yeni Galeri blokları oluşturun ve eski galerileri eşleşecek şekilde otomatik olarak dönüştürün.
- Bloklar halinde bağlantı metnini biçimlendirirken değişiklikleri geri alın ve yineleyin.
- Gönderileri yeniden bloga eklerken ve diğer uygulamalardan metin paylaşırken daha hızlı yükleyin.
- Standart temalı sitelerde önceden biçimlenmiş blok tipi için arka plan renklerine göz atın.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
18.9：
- 在段落区块中，使用任意颜色突出显示文本。
- 创建采用最新设计的画廊区块，自动转换旧画廊区块，保持风格一致。
- 在区块中设置链接文本的格式时，撤消和重新更改。
- 重新发布博文和分享来自其他应用程序的文本时，更快加载。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
18.9:
- 可用任意顏色醒目標示段落區塊中的文字。
- 加入全新設計的畫廊區塊，並可自動將舊版畫廊轉換至新版區塊。
- 在變更區塊內鏈結文字時可復原與重做。
- 從其他應用程式轉發或分享文章時更加快速。
- 可在使用標準主題的網站上看見預先格式化區塊的背景顏色。
</zh-TW>
