<en-US>
- We tweaked the upload error text in media upload blocks.
- Animated GIFs now come with a GIF badge.
- Block setting changes to ordered lists now appear in the editor.
- You can disable Weekly Roundup notifications for all sites in App Info.
</en-US>
<ar>
19.5:
- قمنا بتعديل نص خطأ الرفع في مكوِّنات رفع الوسائط.
- تأتي صور GIF المتحركة الآن مزوَّدة بشارة GIF.
- تظهر الآن تغييرات إعداد المكوِّن على القوائم المرتبة في المحرِّر.
- يمكنك تعطيل تنبيهات الموجز الأسبوعي لجميع المواقع في معلومات التطبيق.
</ar>
<de-DE>
19.5:
- Wir haben den Text bei Upload-Fehlern in Blöcken zum Hochladen von Medien aktualisiert.
- Animierte GIFs haben jetzt ein GIF-Badge.
- Änderungen an den Blockeinstellungen für sortierte Listen werden jetzt im Editor angezeigt.
- Du kannst die Benachrichtigungen mit wöchentlichen Zusammenfassungen für alle Websites unter „App-Info“ deaktivieren.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
19.5:
- Hemos modificado el texto que informa de un error de subida en los bloques de subida de medios.
- Ahora, los GIF animados vienen con una insignia de GIF.
- Ahora, los cambios que realices en los ajustes del bloque para las listas ordenadas aparecerán en el editor.
- Puedes desactivar las notificaciones del Resumen semanal para todos los sitios en Información de la aplicación.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
19.5 :
- Nous avons apporté quelques retouches au message d’erreur concernant le chargement de contenu multimédia dans les blocs.
- Les GIF animés affichent désormais un badge distinctif.
- La structure des blocs a changé pour permettre l’affichage des listes ordonnées dans l’éditeur.
- Vous pouvez désactiver les notifications de résumé hebdomadaire pour tous vos sites depuis la section d’informations de l’application.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
19.5:
- שינינו את הטקסט בשגיאת ההעלאה בבלוקים של העלאת מדיה.
- קובצי GIF מונפשים כעת מופיעים עם עיטור 'GIF'.
- שינויים בהגדרות הבלוק לרשימות מסודרות מופיעים כעת בעורך.
- אפשר להשבית את ההודעות של 'סיכום שבועי' לכל האתרים דרך 'פרטי האפליקציה'.
</iw-IL>
<id>
19.5:
- Kami menyesuaikan teks error saat mengunggah di blok unggah media.
- Animasi GIF kini dilengkapi lencana GIF.
- Perubahan pengaturan blok pada daftar berurutan kini ditampilkan di editor.
- Anda dapat menonaktifkan pemberitahuan Ringkasan Mingguan untuk semua situs di Info Aplikasi.
</id>
<it-IT>
19.5:
- Abbiamo fatto piccole modifiche al testo dell'errore di caricamento nei blocchi per il caricamento di elementi multimediali.
- Le GIF animate ora sono dotate di un badge GIF.
- Le modifiche delle impostazioni del blocco negli elenchi ordinati ora appaiono nell'editor.
- Puoi disattivare le notifiche del Resoconto settimanale per tutti i siti nelle Info sull'app.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
19.5:
- メディアアップロードブロックのアップロードエラーテキストを微調整しました。
- アニメーション GIF に GIF バッジが表示されるようになりました。
- 番号つきリストに対するブロック設定の変更がエディターに表示されるようになりました。
- 1週間のまとめ通知をすべてのサイトに対してアプリ情報で無効にできます。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
19.5:
- 미디어 업로드 블록의 업로드 오류 텍스트를 조정했습니다.
- 이제는 GIF 애니메이션에 GIF 배지가 표시됩니다.
- 순서 있는 목록의 블록 설정 변경 사항이 이제는 편집기에 표시됩니다.
- 앱 정보에서 모든 사이트에 대한 주간 총정리 알림을 비활성화하실 수 있습니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
19.5:
- We hebben de tekst van uploadfouten in media-uploadblokken aangepast.
- Bewegende GIF's zijn nu voorzien van een GIF-badge.
- Gewijzigde blokinstellingen naar geordende lijsten verschijnen nu in de editor.
- Je kunt meldingen voor het Wekelijkse overzicht uitschakelen voor alle sites onder App-info.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
19.5:
- Ajustamos o texto do erro de upload nos blocos de upload de mídia.
- GIFs animados agora vêm com um emblema de GIF.
- Agora as alterações de configuração de bloco em listas ordenadas aparecem no editor.
- É possível desativar as notificações do resumo semanal para todos os sites nas informações do aplicativo.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
19.5:
— Мы немного изменили текст ошибки загрузки в блоках загрузки медиафайлов.
— Анимированные изображения GIF теперь отмечены значком GIF.
— Изменения в упорядоченных списках в настройках блоков теперь отображаются в редакторе.
— Вы можете отключить уведомления о сводке за неделю для всех сайтов в разделе информации о приложении.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
19.5:
- Vi har ändrat texten för uppladdningsfel i mediauppladdningsblock.
- Animerade GIF-bilder har nu ett GIF-märke.
- Blockinställningsändringar av sorterade listor visas nu i redigeraren.
- Du kan inaktivera veckosammanfattningsnotiser för alla webbplatser i Appinformation.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
19.5:
- Medya yükleme bloklarındaki yükleme hatası metninde ince ayar yaptık.
- Hareketli GIF'lerde artık bir GIF rozeti görüntüleniyor.
- Sıralı listelerdeki blok ayarı değişiklikleri artık düzenleyicide de görünüyor.
- Uygulama Bilgisi'nde tüm siteler için Haftalık Özet bildirimlerini devre dışı bırakabilirsiniz.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
19.5：
- 我们调整了媒体上传区块中的上传错误文本。
- 现在，动画 GIF 带有 GIF 徽章。
- 现在，对有序列表的区块设置更改显示在编辑器中。
- 您可以在“应用程序信息”中为所有站点禁用每周综述通知。 
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
19.5：
- 我們調整了媒體上傳區塊的上傳錯誤文字。
- GIF 動畫現在會附上 GIF 徽章。
- 對已排序清單的區塊設定變更現在會顯示於編輯器中。
- 你可在「應用程式資訊」中停用所有網站的每週綜合整理通知。
</zh-TW>
