<en-US>
- Font size and line height are now supported for block themes.
- Add new stat cards in the Settings menu on the Stats screen.
- When changing the media in an Image block that’s also a post’s Featured Image, get a prompt to replace the Featured Image.
- Share text, images, and video in the app using your device’s Share action.
</en-US>
<ar>
19.2:
- تم دعم حجم الخط وارتفاع السطر الآن لقوالب المكوِّن.
- أضف بطاقات إحصاءات جديدة في قائمة الإعدادات على شاشة الإحصاءات.
- عند تغيير الوسائط في مكوِّن صورة يكون كذلك صورة بارزة للتدوينة، احصل على مطالبة لاستبدال الصورة البارزة.
- شارك النص والصور ومقاطع الفيديو في التطبيق باستخدام إجراء مشاركة جهازك.
</ar>
<de-DE>
19.2:
– Schriftgröße und Zeilenhöhe für Block-Themes werden jetzt unterstützt.
– Neue Statistikkarten im Einstellungsmenü des Statistikbildschirms hinzugefügt.
– Beim Ändern von Medien in einem Bildblock, der auch als Beitragsbild verwendet wird, kannst du jetzt auch gleich das Beitragsbild ersetzen.
– Du kannst jetzt Text, Bilder und Videos in der App mit der Freigabefunktion deines Geräts teilen.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
19.2:
- Ahora, los temas de bloques son compatibles con el tamaño de la fuente y la altura de la línea.
- Añade nuevas fichas de estadísticas en el menú de Ajustes de la pantalla de Estadísticas.
- Al cambiar los archivos de medios en un bloque de imagen (que también sea la imagen destacada de una entrada), recibirás un aviso para sustituir esta imagen destacada.
- Comparte texto, imágenes y videos en la aplicación mediante la acción Compartir de tu dispositivo.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
19.2 :
- Les tailles de police et les hauteurs de ligne sont désormais prises en charge dans les thèmes de blog.
- De nouvelles cartes de statistiques sont disponibles dans le menu Réglages de l’écran des statistiques.
- Lorsque vous remplacez le média d’un bloc d’image qui correspond à l’image mise en avant d’un article, une demande de confirmation du changement s’affiche.
- Partagez du texte, des images et des vidéo depuis l’application grâce à l’option Partager de votre appareil.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
19.2:
- גודל הגופן וגובה השורה נתמכים עכשיו בערכות עיצוב של בלוקים.
- הוספת כרטיסים חדשים של נתונים סטטיסטיים בתפריט ההגדרות במסך 'נתונים סטטיסטיים'.
- בזמן שינוי המדיה בבלוק תמונה שגם משמש כתמונה מרכזית של פוסט, תופיע הודעה לגבי החלפת התמונה המרכזית.
- שיתוף טקסט, תמונות ווידאו באפליקציה באמצעות פעולת השיתוף של המכשיר.
</iw-IL>
<id>
19.2:
- Sekarang ukuran font dan ketinggian baris didukung untuk tema blok.
- Tambahan kartu statistik baru pada menu Pengaturan di layar Statistik.
- Ketika mengubah media pada blog Gambar yang juga merupakan Gambar Andalan pos, Anda akan melihat permintaan konfirmasi untuk mengganti Gambar Andalan.
- Bagikan teks, gambar, dan video pada aplikasi menggunakan tindakan Bagikan dari perangkat Anda.
</id>
<it-IT>
19.2:
- La dimensione del carattere e l'altezza della linea sono ora supportati per i temi dei blocchi.
- Aggiungi nuove carte statistiche nel menu Impostazioni della schermata Statistiche.
- Quando modifichi l'elemento multimediale in un blocco Immagine che è anche immagine in evidenza in un articolo, visualizzerai una richiesta per sostituire l'immagine in evidenza.
- Condividi testo, immagini e video nell'app utilizzando l'azione Condividi del tuo dispositivo.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
19.2:
- ブロックテーマのフォントサイズと行の高さが調整できるようになりました。
- 「統計情報」画面の「設定」メニューに新しい統計カードを追加しました。
- 投稿の「アイキャッチ画像」でもある「画像」ブロック内のメディアを変更する場合、「アイキャッチ画像」の置き換えを知らせるプロンプトが表示されるようになりました。
- 端末の「共有」アクションを使用して、アプリ内でテキスト、画像、動画を共有できます。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
19.2:
- 이제 글꼴 크기와 줄 높이가 블록 테마에 대해 지원됩니다.
- 통계 화면의 설정 메뉴에 새 통계 카드를 추가합니다.
- 글의 특성 이미지이기도 한 이미지 블록에서 미디어를 변경하면 특성 이미지를 교체하라는 메시지가 표시됩니다.
- 기기의 공유 작업을 통해 텍스트, 이미지 및 비디오를 공유합니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
19.2:
- Lettertypegrootte en regelafstand worden nu ondersteund voor blokthema's.
- Nieuwe statistiekenkaarten zijn toegevoegd aan het Instellingenmenu in het Statistiekenvenster.
- Als je de media veranderd in een afbeeldingblok dat ook een uitgelichte afbeelding is, krijg je vanaf nu een prompt om de uitgelichte afbeelding te vervangen.
- Deel tekst, afbeeldingen en video's in de app met de optie Delen van je apparaat.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
19.2:
- Altura de linha e tamanho de fonte agora são compatíveis com temas de blocos.
- Novos cartões de estatísticas adicionados ao menu Configurações na tela Estatísticas.
- Ao alterar a mídia em um bloco de imagem que também é usada como uma imagem destacada em um post, aparecerá uma mensagem perguntando se você quer substituir a imagem destacada.
- Compartilhamento de textos, imagens e vídeos no app com a ação Compartilhar do dispositivo.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
19.2:
— Теперь размер шрифта и высота строк поддерживаются для тем блоков.
— Создание новых карточек статистики с помощью меню «Настройки» на экране статистики.
— При изменении медиафайла в блоке «Изображение», который также используется в качестве избранного изображения в записи, появится запрос о замене избранного изображения.
— Предоставление доступа к тексту, изображениям и видео в приложении с помощью команды «Поделиться» на вашем устройстве.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
19.2:
- Textstorlek och radhöjd stöds nu för blockteman.
- Lägg till nya statistikkort i menyn Inställningar på skärmen Statistik.
- Vid ändring av media i ett bildblock som också används som utvald bild för ett inlägg visas en prompt som gör det möjligt att byta ut den utvalda bilden.
- Dela text, bilder och videoklipp i appen med hjälp av åtgärden Dela på din enhet.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
19.2:
- Yazı tipi boyutu ve satır yüksekliği artık blok temalar için destekleniyor.
- İstatistikler ekranındaki Ayarlar menüsüne yeni istatistik kartları ekleyebilirsiniz.
- Bir Görsel blokunda, aynı zamanda bir Öne Çıkan Görsel olan ortamı değiştirmek istediğinizde, Öne Çıkan Görsel ile ilgili bir değiştirme istemi alın.
- Cihazınızdaki Paylaş eylemini kullanarak uygulamada metin, resim ve video paylaşın
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
19.2：
- 现在，区块主题支持字体大小和行高。
- 在“统计数据”界面的“设置”菜单中添加了新统计数据卡。
- 在“图片区块”中更改媒体（同时也是一个特色图片）时，系统会弹出提示，询问您是否替换该特色图片。
- 使用您设备的“共享”操作在应用程序中共享文本、图片和视频。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
19.2：
- 現已支援區塊佈景主題的字型大小和行高。
- 在「統計資料」畫面的「設定」選單中新增統計資料卡片。
- 若圖片區塊中的媒體同時也做為文章特色圖片，變更該媒體時會收到取代該特色圖片的提示。
- 使用裝置的「分享」動作來分享應用程式中的文字、圖片和影片。
</zh-TW>
