<en-US>
We have made a couple of handy tweaks to the Block editor: The Embed block now gives you a sneak preview when you add something from YouTube or Twitter (more providers to come); and when you go to insert a block and nothing is found, there is now a no results view.
</en-US>
<ar>
18.2:
لقد أجرينا بعض التعديلات العملية على محرِّر المكوِّن: يمنحك مكوِّن التضمين الآن معاينة مسبقة عندما تضيف شيئًا ما من يوتيوب أو تويتر (المزيد من المزوِّدين في المستقبل)؛ وعندما تنتقل لإدراج مكوِّن ولا يتم العثور على أي شيء، لا يوجد الآن أي طريقة عرض نتائج.
</ar>
<de-DE>
18.2:
Wir haben ein paar praktische Änderungen am Block-Editor vorgenommen: Der Embed-Block bietet jetzt eine Vorschau, wenn du Inhalte aus YouTube oder Twitter (und bald noch von weiteren Anbietern) einfügst. Und wenn du einen Block einfügst und nichts gefunden wird, siehst du jetzt die Anzeige, dass keine Ergebnisse vorhanden sind.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
18.2:
Hemos hecho un par de mejoras en el Editor de bloques: ahora el bloque de incrustar muestra una vista previa cuando añades contenido de YouTube o de Twitter (próximamente se añadirán más proveedores). Además, si quieres insertar un bloque pero no se encuentra nada, ahora aparece una vista sin resultados. 
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
18.2 :
Nous avons apporté quelques modifications pratiques à l’éditeur de blocs : le bloc de contenu embarqué vous donne désormais un premier aperçu lorsque vous effectuez un ajout depuis YouTube ou Twitter (plus de fournisseurs prochainement) ; et lorsque vous essayez d’insérer un bloc introuvable, un message indique qu’aucun résultat n’est disponible.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
18.2:
ביצענו כמה שינויים קטנים ומועילים לעורך הבלוקים: בלוק ההטמעה כעת מאפשר לך לראות תצוגה מקדימה כאשר מוסיפים תוכן מ-YouTube או מטוויטר (בקרוב נוסיף עוד ספקים). בנוסף, כאשר עוברים להוספת בלוק אבל לא מוצאים שום דבר, כעת המידע שאין תוצאות מופיע בתצוגה.
</iw-IL>
<id>
18.2:
Kami melakukan beberapa penyesuaian bermanfaat untuk editor Blok: Blok Sematan sekarang dilengkapi pratinjau singkat untuk konten yang ditambahkan dari YouTube atau Twitter (penyedia lainnya akan hadir); dan saat blok dimasukkan dan tidak ada konten yang ditemukan, tidak ada hasil akan muncul di tampilan.
</id>
<it-IT>
18.2:
Abbiamo apportato un paio di utili miglioramenti all'editor a blocchi: il blocco Incorporamenti ora ti offre un assaggio di anteprima quando aggiungi qualcosa da YouTube o Twitter (sono in arrivo altri fornitori); e quando vai a inserire un blocco e non trovi nulla, ora viene mostrata una visualizzazione "nessun risultato".
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
18.2:
ブロックエディターにいくつかの便利な機能が追加されました。YouTube や Twitter (今後他のプロバイダーにも対応予定) からコンテンツを追加すると、埋め込みブロックでプレビューが見られるようになりました。また、ブロックを挿入しようとして何も見つからなかった場合は、「見つかりませんでした」と表示されるようになりました。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
18.2:
블록 편집기에서 몇 가지를 편리하게 조정했습니다. 이제 YouTube 또는 Twitter에서 무언가를 추가하면 살짝 미리보기가 임베드 블록에서 제공됩니다(공급업체 추가 예정). 그리고 블록 삽입으로 이동했는데 아무것도 찾을 수 없으면 이제는 결과 없음 보기가 나타납니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
18.2:
We hebben enkele kleine maar nuttige aanpassingen aangebracht aan de blokeditor: Het insluitblok toont nu een voorbeeldweergave wanneer je iets van YouTube of Twitter toevoegt (in de toekomst meer platformen). En voor wanneer je een blok toevoegt maar er niets wordt gevonden, is er nu een weergave voor geen resultaten.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
18.2:
Fizemos alguns ajustes práticos no editor de blocos: o bloco de mídia incorporada agora fornece uma prévia quando você adiciona mídia do YouTube ou Twitter (em breve mais provedores). Além disso, quando você quer inserir um bloco e não encontra nada, agora aparece uma visualização "Nenhum resultado".
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
18.2:
Мы внесли пару полезных изменений в редактор блоков: блок "Вставка" теперь поддерживает предварительный просмотр при добавлении содержимого из YouTube или Twitter (скоро будут добавлены другие поставщики); если при использовании функции вставки блока ничего не найдено, отображается вид "Нет результатов".
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
18.2:
Vi har gjort några praktiska ändringar i blockredigeraren: Inbäddningsblocket ger dig nu en förhandsvisning när du lägger till något från YouTube eller Twitter (fler leverantörer kommer) och när du ska infoga ett block och ingenting hittas visas nu en vy utan resultat.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
18.2:
Blok düzenleyicide kullanışlı birkaç değişiklik yaptık: Gömülü blok artık YouTube veya Twitter'dan bir şey eklediğinizde size bir önizleme görüntülüyor (yakında daha fazla sağlayıcı sunulacaktır). Bir blok eklemeye gittiğinizde ve hiçbir şey bulunamadığında da artık sonuç görünümü görüntülenmeyecektir.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
18.2：
我们对区块编辑器进行了一些便捷调整：借助嵌入区块，您现在从 YouTube 或 Twitter（即将推出更多提供商）添加内容时，可以先睹为快；此外，当您插入区块，但没有找到任何内容时，现在会有“无结果”视图。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
18.2：
我們對區塊編輯器進行了一些實用的調整：在嵌入區塊中從 Youtube 或 Twitter (之後會支援更多服務商) 新增內容時，現在可以迅速預覽畫面；插入區塊卻找不到內容時，現在也會顯示無結果畫面。
</zh-TW>
